This one for the room, the merchants and the peddlers, the fake deep fraud department.
Let's go.
You bring atmosphere, a little fake concern, then a volunteer, tear you load up a prom,
let the chatbot talk, then strut back proud like you prove your talk.
You call it research, I call it cosplay, a smear in slow motion with the church girl,
cliche, big words, dark tone, thumbnail rage.
You're at a sermon at shame, now they're nonsense, got makeup in a brand new name.
Welcome to this show with the link backstage.
What up, though?
How are you?
One second.
My heart, man.
How you been, man?
OK.
I'm surviving.
I'm surviving beating a lot of other people, you know.
You got to be careful, man, you know?
This mess here has caused a lot of drama divides, you know?
You know, a lot of divides between people, you know, and it's getting crazy, man, you know, but what can we do, man?
You know, you got Bita, you know, Docs and people that used to be her close friends,
you know. And it's so controversial, too. You know, Bita's been like, you know, saying,
oh, you know, I'm a thief because she said there's this whole, like, meme that I stole from the Korean liquor store that I go to.
They say I stole coffee or a cigar or something.
You never tried to steal though right I never did I never did and I was a misunderstanding at the store
But then she'll say oh, I still copy okay, so yeah, okay
So I got my copy got it with points today
I have points on this apps like I'm free coffee
Okay, and I can get that refilled all day until they close at one third, but you know, there's no one to say
Be that steel stream yard
You know who pops down?
Well, yeah, that's what I said.
I mean, it's like, okay, I can say she's smart
and she plays the system, like I do with maybe a copy,
or I can say, oh, she's still a streamer
because she just gets to account after account
after account and be used free,
never upgrades or anything, right?
And use, it's like, do they really care?
No, they don't really care.
We made it to say, but she's gonna say that about me.
Like, I'm some kind of thief, oh, I'm so cheap.
Wait, wait, she doesn't like to save money.
I mean, it's like,
Wait, wait, people are so offended that McDonald's gives me a refill.
I mean, I have to ask them.
It's not like I jump over the counter and run to the back and do it, you know, against their will.
They take the cup from me, they refill it.
Sometimes they see when it was bought and it was bought maybe several hours earlier.
They never care, not once.
Every single time they've refilled my coffee, so.
I don't know. I don't know. I mean, it's like, that's the worst thing I do.
Am I going to hell for that?
I mean, it's like every little thing, everything's so overblown.
It's crazy. But what's the clip you gave me?
You gave me the beat of the show yesterday?
Is there a particular part we should watch or?
Yeah, yeah, definitely. Yeah.
It's some new shit.
You know what? You know, midnight, right?
You know, that beat of, you know, went hard.
Yeah, I mean, I was in the chat and she was being mean.
Yeah, she was she was fucking being disrespectful to the midnight and matter of fact
Can you can you pull that up and go to the 14 hour and 49 minute mark? Oh my god
It's over 14 hours long. Oh, yeah when she's drunk. Oh, yeah. Yeah when she gets the drink and it's always over 12 hours
You know
Yeah, 49 minute 14 hour 49 minute Mario
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And what's crazy site, you know,
is the fact that, you know,
she said something in there that amazed me.
You know, I'm like, wow.
She said, well, midnight, you know,
I lost my mother before you lost your mother.
So, you know.
You know, like, she got a higher right, a bigger right, you know, to degrade and disrespect,
you know, midnight's, you know, mother, you know, well, I lost my mother first.
I should get sympathy, you know, I lost her when I was 14 years old.
I mean, that's the opposite of like, you know, and then Alexander stings up about my, my dad and like, you know, she lost her dad too.
Like, you know, she lost her dad more recently, but she's like, Oh, well, I should be already be over it.
You know, it's like, she's, she's, I'm not, but she did that. She's saying, I don't know. I won't go into it. I don't want to get her back.
But here, let's let them be noticed.
I'll play this clip. So this is the surviving beat. Oh, so by the beat is I don't know
Present this is from rumble
panel versus vlds
14 minutes 49 seconds. This is a beta going after
No, no, I said I said 14 hours and 49 minutes 14 hours. Yeah, that's what I said. Oh, okay
Yeah, this is poor men that poor men that is being attacked
Poor men that is being attacked and beat us chat. I mean, it's me shocking
You ready to yell, though? I'll pull my hands.
I kinda love listening to Persian music and having 60 people listening to Persian music.
Shout out to Persian music. Love it or hate it, that's what I'm doing right now, y'all.
You like it or you don't? I don't know how to drop the lingus pen.
You're not going to join anyways, my night. You're just going to, yeah.
And you're probably a dude, anyway. You're a dude. There's no way you could be a female.
Oh.
Nobody's a fucking like, you know.
Total dude.
A whole penis.
I'm drunk and stupid
Your grandmother your ancestor your aunt everybody in your whole being
Pew what you gonna do about it?
Just all bought it fucking master quesadilla
That was a curse that was a Persian spell my god
During witchcraft before our eyes
Go suck some fucking cake to turtle fucking big fat rashi as poor and let's see how long you can tolerate on her
Chat talking shit your ancestors you heard that midnight
You heard that?
That's your outro
Your fucking ancestors
Oh
My god
I don't say it to you bum gang. I don't say it to someone
We say to the fucking people I want to say it to you
Oh you pause it real quick, pause it, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said,
She said, I won't say it to Samman or Brumba.
I'm saying it to Midnight.
She's not going to talk about Samman's mom or Julio's.
She's just going to talk about Midnight.
She'll say all kinds of things about my cats.
And she'll say, oh, but Samman, he's such an animal lover.
And he's so gentle.
And he loved Ninji and stuff like that.
But she'll say, oh, where's Trix?
Marbles wears wears magic. It's stuff like that. She knows what happens like those cats are fine. All those cats are fine, but
You know and she's trying to rub that in like it's like I'm some horrible person because my cats are indoor outdoor cats and
Sometimes get assimilated into the neighborhood or different different living situations. I mean, I don't know. I mean, it's like
Where are they actually? I'm sure there's neighbors. I mean, it's like, you know, cuz tux came back for like in a little while and
You know the assembly neighbor, it's a nice neighbor. I mean, it's like
You know check might come back check might come back in a couple months. You know, like, you know
We never know it's like you know, because well, you know, he kind of like probably started to start to wander a little bit because
You know, there's like there's cats meowing outside and heat and stuff like that around the neighborhood and stuff
and so they tend to wander a little bit, but
you know
don't mean
People can try to rub in it. I look for the cats. I mean, it's like I'm always looking in next door if I see if and like, you know
Here we have a guest we have a guest. We have I to survive beta coming to this show
Let's see who's here. Oh my gosh. Okay, so somebody else survived beta. Okay, another survivor
Welcome on my I think it's we pee. Oh my god. We pee
This is 3p. Hi, tell your story about beta
No, I want to be honest, although this is a safe hub here for those survivors of Vita.
I too am a victim of hers.
Are you a victim?
Okay, what happened?
Well, a couple of months ago, she accused me of being the worst thing you could accuse
of anyone being.
Oh my God.
She accused me of being that.
my parents, my family, my non-existent kids.
Oh, my God.
She doesn't really respect anybody.
She doesn't respect anyone.
And yesterday, the clip, Psych, that you played,
I loved how she was the one to always go to your loved ones first,
even though she always claims...
She doesn't do that. You're probably pissing her off, but you never mentioned her parents
No, nothing. No, he always went there first
No, she said I mentioned my dad. She said my dad had a big big nose. My mom looked like the cat woman
You know that woman with all the surgery in New York like which is so untrue
I too mentally
psychologically
and possibly physically, and my victim would beat him.
Yeah.
Physically?
Possibly. Possibly.
What did she do to you? She touched you?
Um, she said I'm ugly, and I looked at myself in the mirror,
and I thought twice about what I really am.
Oh, my God. Never look.
You know.
Yeah.
Okay.
Dangerous, you're doing her more what she has to say. Let's hear a little bit
She told me she had higher ups. She said I got higher ups. I got higher ups
I'm like, what do you got like what do you mean? Is it like the witchcraft shit or
It's like the Wizard of Oz it's like the Wizard of Oz I got that her perfect analogy
I think like, you know, she wants to be the Wizard of Oz have all the secrets and or but she's actually the wicked witch
Yeah
Yeah, and there's clips out there where she denied speaking badly about midnight's mom, you know
And now it's coming out people are finding these clips where she was fucking because she deletes her lies as everybody
You know, you know, she deletes them, you know, and now that we found this clip, you know
It's only a matter of time before I find clip where she was talking about
Or she was denying speaking about, you know, midnight mom, you know what I mean?
Like I'm gonna put those two together.
Oh, I mean, I teach you how to go through all the transcripts and just have that and like search them
and then you'll be able to find all this information quicker.
I mean, you need, you're doing such good work.
You need to be compiling this.
We need to build a wing in the codex.
A wiki, maybe get a wiki on beta or a fucking Reddit page.
What about a Reddit page?
And we even read it, we're gonna have to make a whole book about it actually, like you know,
surviving Vita, we have all the survivors get together, we have parties and stuff like that too.
She's trying to convince us to see the bartender for Spanish sling word for fact, oh my god,
she tried to get it, thing murdered.
Oh my god, she's in the chat. I don't want you to know. She threatens to like, you know
Sue sue for anything. Let's just play more with brother. Well, she did threaten me a couple days ago
She said she knows things and those people and oh my god, be that I will regret everything
I'm fucking K to turn. Oh my god. Is that her? I'm scared
Sorry, I thought this was the safe haven
okay thank you from getting if you don't like it you can divorce me that's my style that
fuck these motherfuckers condom imagine if you're playing this song your baby and then it's like
and you looked up at those are your parents she always plays that song it's delicious
i imagine that sometimes when i look at that picture she didn't do anything
read the comments read it you want to be my mom is fucking drunk and fucking
stupid I'm gonna give everything that you said about me as we fucking go back
and forth
Listen, don't tell me she didn't fucking say nothing to me or he
Whatever the fuck I want from gang you want to be on Monday
Wow threatening people to on my
Ain't that crazy?
Fucking skincast bitch is not gonna tell me I'm drunk and stupid her mom is drunk and stupid
She's fucking evil Chad. She's evil
Say anything to me. Oh, we have a guest coming. Oh, no
Is it another I just talked about your mother. Yes, I did Wow your mother fuck your fucking
Turn your phone back on, turn your phone back on.
You're fucking ever judging me.
No, no branding Q in here.
No branding Q.
I never hurt you. I never fucking hurt anybody.
Fuck your mother for raising you.
Okay, Mennai?
What you gonna do about it?
Fuck your mom.
Hello, fuck your mom.
You're out of here.
Fuck your mom. What you gonna do about it?
No branding Q on this family.
Watch your fucking mouth when you talk to me, bitch.
Cry a little bit in different chat
Your whole ass, dude
Come bro gang
Your near brother is like
I'm not brandy Q you fuck
You love your mother?
Karen, you were shown back on.
Oh, shit.
I love my mother, too.
Because don't fucking judge me.
Fuck you.
I bet I love my mother before I.
OK.
Well, I mean, it's.
My mother, Ronald, 14.
Won't you lose your mom?
No, listen, listen, listen.
When you lose your mom?
I'll see.
He said when you lose your mom
We lost our mom before midnight
When you decided that it's okay for Kate to turtle to say that my fucking dad should have a heart attack
On you're like I like Kate fuck your mother and fuck everything you stand for I lost my mom at 14
I bet you money you lost your mom way after that
Fuck you and everything. What does that matter?
Why does that matter?
Listen.
Oh, she's evil, dude.
I'm not taking it back.
OK. All right.
You fucking watch your fucking mouth.
I lost my mother.
I lost my mom before you did.
I bet you. I bet you I did.
So shut your fucking matter or fate.
God damn.
The fucks.
my mom has 14 but I still have to get the disgrace of being dogged telling my dad had
fucking touched me and all the shit that you stand for and you go over to fucking cage a turtle
fuck you and your mother put together okay nobody gives two fucks your outros are gonna be
Fuck you midnight when you understand what I'm coming from I understand when you're coming from bitch
Midnight listen to the advice did she die before you were like fucking 14
My mom died when I was 14. Don't sit there and say my mom died and talk about people's fucking family
You started this fucking shit. Go fuck yourself. I don't give two fucks about you
Your intro and outro is always gonna be puked to me from now on, okay?
I don't give two fucking fucks the same fucking trauma. You've had a lot of people have except you're an alt
Think you sit there and you bully until you get your fucking way bitch you ain't getting your way with me today
You're probably a dude. I don't give two fucks. It's my fucking ass. Okay, my night. Okay. I
Just go quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly
Vinito finito finito
Never assume your electric bill is accurate if there's an EV charger anywhere on the street
Your smart meter can't tell the difference between your power and their surges and you pay for both
No matter how much you try, your power bill doesn't go down.
My bitch. Bye.
Dumb bitch.
The fuck is my family gonna be fucking?
The funny thing is okay when everybody talks about my ex, my family,
my dad, my mom, but I said one fucking thing.
Fuck you on everything you said.
Don't you make fun of salmon every day and night? We're saying my mom my mom fuck you
Go fuck yourself. Go fuck yourself bitch. Go fuck yourself
We are okay without a midnight
I'm only okay with midnight if she takes the link otherwise. She ain't no
Ivana shout out to you for taking the link
Ivana you took the link
let me see what else we have you see do you want to see what happened on good times the other day
i wonder this is when he when he when he and hold on i went on a good time to the very end
and here's what happened shit really happened i'm gonna plug in the camera that um pizza gave me
30 he gave me the money for it or buy and i'm gonna charge it up that thing is complicated
But I'll do a short little premiere of my garden
Megapodity
Wow, somebody actually remember me when I used to play movies on rumble. Yeah, that's kind of funny
I'm gonna go out and try to clean up my bamboo a little bit. My mom thinks it looks messy
I like the way it looks. It's a natural forest. It's just growing
My mom's like that's not a forest. I'm like, yeah, it is like it's beautiful
Forest took me five years to grow forest. What are you talking about?
Well, I'm out of here. You guys have a good one. That's all the guy didn't cop that recipe
earlier yesterday. The guys can get drunk as shit. Start pulling people. I'm right back. Wait a second.
You told me he said, I do whatever I want. I'm a cop. I'm drunk. I can shoot you. I'm a cop.
I don't know if that was called body camera footage or not.
Notice no one's been able to get the body camera footage from that arrest.
Because he had his shit shut off.
Ha ha ha ha.
God damn cops are on here.
They're Dukes of Hazard or some shit.
They're a rascopy coal train.
Now more bad.
I think some were fucking deployed in the war or something, they're in the military because they are psycho as shit.
All the ones that are on my age are normal.
Anyways, yeah. It's time to go. I'm gonna plug that camera in. Hopefully nothing, it doesn't fry anything.
Should work.
Yeah, he said no, he told me when when you're born, but it was like you'd be called me or I went on a show
I went backstage and he's like, no, I do that. You know what's like? He's like you're a psychopath
Okay, who's beta's kiddies fed up with the lines, but feeling trapped in an endless stream of propaganda
Do you want the tools to break free and kick your awakening journey into high gear at DSMP dot IO we don't
Think YouTube runs live streaming think again the biggest live streams in the US are happening on rumble
And now launching your own stream is easier than ever with a rumble studio
One
Low batteries he like
I think you're brutally on low battery and I'm trying to check to see if it's lying.
Tender.
Okay.
Wait, that's me.
I hope you're having a slight nourishment.
The cycle of contact.
Let's see.
Breathe.
These days I'm only listening to plus three, plus three
Every time I hear you, I think you're there with me
There's a big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big
We sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing, we sing
Oh, tender.
I think you're with me.
OK, man.
Oh, yeah.
That's the thing.
You're trying to antagonize him.
OK.
Really?
Your karma's coming too, Barry.
They caught me, they caught me today with a fake cake, I spied though, I didn't give a fuck, Degas.
To where everybody at leader people want to antagonize psyche a little bit and it's what can makes me happy
Let me see what he's saying little batteries that he'd like. He's let's see what he's bitching about
Sometimes funny to hear this time talk
Let's oh yeah, him raging is fucking hilarious. What is he playing?
He's probably watching me, I'm watching him.
I'm watching him for those that beat his stream tonight.
Where he had a...
What do you have to say in my name?
A-O-T-N-I-G-G-E-R.
Oh!
He called me a sand and I-I-G-G-E-R last night.
Oh my God.
But he called me a sand and word with a heart.
Or last night in a fucking life.
I'd like to go into a 24-to-ever.
I like how Clonsy likes to be so invested now.
He's almost even asking about Amanda.
Like Amanda, you say what's your deal with Amanda like Amanda is like some lady that's you know
She's like takes the panel once in a while. She's like from Christine's community. I know I know her
Yeah, like he's asking like he what's your deal with Amanda like come on clumsy now
You're getting becoming a full-ass bitch drama queen
Imagine as a grown-ass man you care about somebody like who's Amanda?
How was your life Salman? I missed uh after I got stopped. I was draining. I was draining. I said it was draining, Bita. It was draining.
I thought it was like raining. I'm like, damn, you got a lot of donuts, huh?
Yeah.
I was like, what do you mean it was raining?
I thought it was draining.
Hey.
Honestly, I never realized how draining it could be, you know, with Ron and fucking Eldle.
Ah.
They kind of are like hype men. They can like, you know fire up the panel and like kind of make shit spicy
But then when they just come out of the blue with the weird shit that you just got to explain yourself
And but you don't have to you know, you just got to be like, oh, what the fuck are you saying doc?
Do we got to go over this all over again? I'm tired of that shit. I'm tired of it. Yeah
It comes with the program here
I
Sometimes I'll become the content, but I eat it
Somebody must have
Boston was cooking today Boston was cooking it out her elbow. That was a fucking cook
I heard she was cooking a full fucking buffet. I was like what?
Yeah, is it on rumble? Yeah, it's on a rumble. Okay. I gotta check it out
Now I was gonna take the panel but I was like fuck this like he's gonna
You don't want to you know, I get it. That's what sometimes I'm glad I could take a panel sometimes
I'll just don't get it man. I like I don't want to I don't gotta
go live
Oh my god, the chat was saying it was fucking fire
Hey chairman. Hey NorCal. NorCal got to say my name. The first thing my name say my name when narcalids are round
You got cut by wrong they could pack yourself up. They could fight wrong
Nobody gets cut by wrong. Nobody
Cook your brain from fucking the dissecting it like you literally want to fucking like take your own brain out
But he can't cook shit
I want things just by screaming and saying yeah
Yeah over people as you're fucking trying to make your point and trapped and come up with some weird
allegations
There's you know old white fucking old white man trying to look as a Mexican and then say that
Say the nigga word
There's no child. No child is every fucking NorCal is like, you know, that's um
Every woman is all he's every race is all in him
Marine hair all white in the paint
Lord Lord bass in Mexico, but he worked with the Mexicans and then he was a the nigga were I never seen oh shit like that be the
Come on, you don't know, you don't know where North Cal, North Cal is from is where the city where, you know, they say what they want. Trust me, trust me.
When both of the North's, yeah. Me and North Cal, I mean, North Cal and I are just fucking will always be like throwing jabs. He'll call me beaks. I'll call him North.
I don't know about you. I don't know. I'm not counting yours. Maybe probably, but mine was
mostly in one setting. One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one,
one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one,
I had a freaking like me and Kate were going out and she had like pictures of me like threatening
Oh, let's you know send pictures new pictures to be does that and give them a heart attack and freaking whatever
I hope he dies and she dies and like all the cat ate her brain all kinds of shit, you know
And she was coming in the chat and she was always be like
Oh, I love Kate, I love Kate.
And then she would throw jabs at like Sam-Man
and like Sam-Man gave his dog fucking lean and blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, I know my life.
Please.
I think she like mentioned Odd family all the time.
I don't know anything about Midnight.
I didn't know like if her mom had passed away or her dad.
I don't know anything.
I was enjoying Odd on her.
Just based on just somebody that would like as I do like a keyword warrior. I've never seen. I don't know shit about
I don't know midnight
at all
And you know what if I heard her feelings, I apologize
But she constantly does the same fucking shit to other people and no apology is going to be
Accepted with her anyway, so
Yeah, people will take like sections how to drain lymph fluid like a true america. This simple trek is transforming life
sounds crazy
But I couldn't skip another ad, so I gave it a shot.
We're at battle, and you don't even know it.
It's called the swollen naked.
I did like 32 hour fucking drinking stream.
I said a lot of fucking shit fucking when I was fucked up.
Now why do you think I'm like, hey.
Yo, it's crazy.
She talk about midnight does all this shit to other people,
but this bitch is talking about midnight
ain't talking about fucking beat a mom.
Midnight ain't out here saying fuck your mom fuck your whole fucking generation fuck your great-grandmother fucking grandmother
This bitch a hypocrite, bro. I'm telling you this bitch a hypocrite, bro
Talk about oh, I don't say nothing about midnight bitch. You fucking talked about his mom
He called you a drunk all midnight day was called beta a fucking drunk because that's what she was at the time right a drunk a
slurring drunk
A Kim slip drunk, a fucking put your underwear on drunk.
That's what she was.
Oh shit, the camera on while I'm putting
my fucking underwear on, cause I got a bush.
Oh my God, look at this bush.
Oh, I got your shit.
I'll go back to the chat for a minute.
Like, come on, man.
No, look, talk to the chat for a minute.
Now you could have kept playing this clip,
but a beater want to act like the fucking moral police.
Oh my God, I'm innocent, I never do anything wrong, bitch.
You don't never do anything wrong
Yeah, yeah, play play to get play the clip
Hey, let me not drink because right now if I fucking drink
I'm gonna fucking cuss the fuck out of elbow tool. Okay. Hey, D. Yeah
She's gonna she gonna attack me
You got same in glazing the shit out of beta. That's all this niggas. It's cheerleader at least when I was up there
I would call beta out just nigga fucking be the glazer. That's all he does was blaze blaze beta 24 fucking seven
Fucking glazinator, man. That's that's what it is new name the glazinator
Somebody put that motherfucking a turn up terminator outfit and call that nigga the glazinator on the fucking big donut
Fucking all glazinator ass motherfucker
Okay, you know, you know how I know this nigga home blazer nadir. This nigga my DM's telling me to stop fucking with beat up
That's how big a fucking blazer nadir same in is he never do that shit
Everybody never do that shit for him. He never hit me up in the DM saying stop talking about
Stop talking about KK
That they get my DMs talking about stop talking about be the why I'm not going that beat up
What you gotta do the whole blazing they just sent back every time he talked about me nigga
Became a clumsy nigga. You're not the same no more my nigga
The nigga everywhere crying about me nigga everywhere. I go in a good. I mean, I'm not even any type
Yeah, but that's nigga Sam and Sam and Sam and Sam and they just go enjoy your yacht nigga
Fuck you weren't about me nigga
Fuck
I never seen a nigga DM me on some gang shit nigga. You can never talk to me nigga
You're you a party blood nigga money money when you get high began your little drink on you want to be a blood nigga
You want to be a gangster, baby?
Won't be blood between me and you what's wrong with being a blood though. I don't know
Yeah, don't be in me by no blood
But I mean, I mean, I don't I don't politics be no fucking DM me about blood
But I mean like what does that mean though?
I'm not a blood, but I have like this bandana. That's like this
Damn be the more blood than DSM shit
At least I got one in every color yeah, I'm about to put you down be the I'm about to put you down be the oh
Eldel I had to go pee right before your stupid fucking comment. Oh my god
You wanted to know oh what happened? Oh like fucking what's his name how to like?
What you heard what his name had a camslip? Oh, I want to see you
And you know what? Those are pictures that were fucking sent to me and it was on a fuck everybody had already seen it
But what do you do Eldo? You keep re-exposing fucking NorCal
You're pink making donations to show his fucking shit
I never have if we have any conversations in private or we go joke or whatever so the fuck what like keep trying bitch
Yes, I'm am I part of the gang now because I have a very standard bandana. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you got at least you got the color
Right, be the eye. I'm part of the Illuminati now
Be the flexing on the g6. I have one in fucking blue and black
It's funny that you can't say that you didn't DM me see how funny is that?
You can't say you never DM me about the blood, huh?
Can't see it's funny. Can't say you can't deny that papa
Well, look you look today you could be blood today. I got you. You know, you could be
Be the king be blood today be the king be blood. You got to fly. Let him be blood today
Oh, huh. That's what the blood at man. Shout to you
Be the be the big homie. No be the let him be blood. That's how to whack one hundred. What he down with be the
What he down with be the
Why do you care like it really?
He's down with OPP be the
All I know he's a fucking north how nor north how w with those
OPV
We'll go let me to go lay them foundation down be the set the program up be the get the program
No food with the fuck no photo is gone from my page and you took those screenshots, but Norquil got
Gone do North. Oh my god. This guy is fucking nuts
Oh my fucking God, are you fucking crazy?
It was like put, it was on Ted's panel.
Every, like as soon as like he calmed up,
bunch of all started making, you know,
the first thing was probably, what's his name?
Bishy and every, like, everybody was like making odds.
You're fucking nuts.
Keep trying, keep trying.
Ella, I've never seen a man bitch so much.
Keep crying.
Hi, Giant Shrimp.
What's up, Eric, as fuck?
This is dumb as hell so I can't hear to pause this shit, but
Go swim with me! Yeah! Yeah!
I've never seen a man turn a flag around.
That's what they do.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Fishi just did it.
I love Fishi. What do you mean through her under the bus?
She just did it recently to the news picture.
That's what they do all the fucking time.
But you know what you did, Aldo?
You keep paying for media to show that shit close up, but you love to like re-expose your child over and over
That's shit from fucking long time ago, but you keep doing that
You care you go to come to you and cry about me nigga
Be the heat this a
Be the he's live right now. Although you move on you're in my chat. Be that I don't wonder you
I'm not gonna lose beat. I'm not gonna lose big T like I lost my beta. Oh my god. That hurt me
You know what lurk all you want. Just don't fucking say my name
Say my name say my name somewhere else run. I'm not around you
Well, how was it how is it? Hi? Hey, it's been that there
I still have some big unbanned people from the chat here.
Give me a minute, I'll unbanned people, hold on a second.
Hear me site, site, be honest.
What's up with the police report, man?
I thought you had a police report then coming, man.
What happened?
You know, I mean, they're aware of the situation
and that's, I mean, I said, I'm not pressing charges.
I've just tried to like get up to a lot
and try to like be aware,
because I've been swatting,
threats about swatting and stuff
and just letting them know, you know, it's a deal.
I got a few crazy,
All right, so do you believe that the reason, do you believe that her hanging out to number is the reason you've been getting slotted and all types of shitting coming to your door.
I know that, I know who else it was.
You know, and he's, you know, it's black, it's kind of Fifth Sage is doing it too.
Like he sends me pictures of Ruby Jimmy's family and stuff and then these terrible messages all read the messages that says so long.
It's like, it's the latest ones I got.
Yeah, he was just up here. What did he say when he came up here?
He said he called me like a bitch or something. I mean, I don't hold on a second. Yeah, he's really rude. Okay. He goes
Yeah, you know, he told me I'm blocking on my phone or answer my phone or turn on my phone
so it says
It says, oh, this one has your name in it.
It says, AI is saying, stop being such a disparate fag,
seeking validation online like a bitch.
And then it has this picture.
I don't know.
Do you know who this person is?
I'm not Barry.
Is that Barry?
I don't know.
It's Barry the Turtle.
Okay, I might be right, Barry the Turtle.
There was almost one in a Pulp Fiction shirt.
I'm not sure if it's Barry the Turtle or not, but.
Okay, then it says-
So who sent you that though?
Piff's day sent you that?
Yeah.
And that's your head on is that you know, no, no, no, I think it's a what's a woman
Then they have like a loot without and then they have this picture
I think he did that because it looked like you know
It looked like me
No, not those, not those.
That's 56, it's Christmas, and then here's the thing,
it says dead white devil on this, I don't know.
So it has to be like.
I don't know, I don't know.
I didn't know 56 was in a mix like that.
You know, DMing you and shit like that, you know what I mean?
I didn't know, man.
He says, hey, what's up?
I've been watching Birdie Joy.
I am busy, but yeah, I'm gonna watch it.
So I don't know who you know, that lady.
And then here's a picture of me.
I like it, it's a good picture of me, actually.
And then, oh, here's a picture of, oh,
and then there's another picture of.
That one, okay, oh, here it says, it says, okay, so it says.
It says, I'm like a bitch, it says, you better stop snitching you, f-ing F-A-G, you better
not, you ain't going anywhere but an AIDS clinic, F-U-Bish, you threatened to K-I-L-L
out, but that's the police, stop sexually harassing Vita and minors, you know that's
the place you make this freak, you lose N-I-G-G-E-R sucker, you're texting yourself fake messages,
you choke cats like n-i-g-g-e-r dick you're free i'm reporting to the police you're a pdf
you're a midget aids n-i-g-g-e-r mudborn f-a-g um then it says like my mom okay you're a monster and
a great great this you act like a psychic literally gives to my channel we don't forget fag all fake
Channel kickers is dismantled now. We're psyche psychos. Your dad is sucking bald and I ggr monkey dick in hell
Your cats hate you. I was talking to your mom. You're a spooky fag. Unblock my stream yards. Don't show my pics, bitch.
You don't have permission to report the pics I sent you and IGG your sucker. I'll make SIG rape you.
Tell Eldo to change his pic or else. Don't show this message, you effing bitch. Told you SIG is going to rape you.
F-A-G-G-O-T bitch.
Karen exposed you. You're a diddler and you're live. Tripp will never help a freak like you. You're scum and suck off P-E-D-O-S.
Yeah.
So that's a chance to sage and do that one. Yeah
Okay, burning joint. Let me see if I can get I can see that is not weird
I'll do a mass and ban after this one. I mean really burning joint us. Actually. I was gonna play this one
Yeah, that's great. So so what what when did I have a picture of is it showing that I got a picture up right now?
It was a picture when you had beta. It was on when I was on probably on Sam man's the other day and you had that
Yeah
It could be, it could be, it could be for very well because of the main sheet, like, you know, but also, yeah, to save something, all that, yeah, because he keeps saying, oh, I'm blocked my stream yard, he says the same kind of language, and then he has those, I think those were him and those pictures, and the other pictures are all many Manson with a razor and his vagina and stuff, and there's, like, a lot of them.
And then there's pictures of like, you know, AM like naked and stuff that's people are sending me
Yeah, but my thing is why don't you just change the number? I don't get y'all man y'all fucking talk about like change the number
Why not change your phone number? I need it for evidence. Okay. Okay. Have you tried changing your phone number?
I mean, I've already changed it before.
I don't feel like changing all the time,
but because it's like a big pain
because I have a lot of stuff attached to it
that I don't want to like get blocked out of.
But here, I'm gonna, I'm gonna show you the video
about the cult and how the worst fears are traffickers.
We're saying the text are sick. I know it's just probably RG and the
Sage and the rest of the candle kicker crew, whatever they are to meet death and the 007 guy
Yeah, you know what's crazy, right?
Beto wants to be like, oh my god, they're dogs and be this down a third
But did she go hard at RG when he did the same thing? He did a whole fucking
He's mushroom out of him. Is it your mod and she goes? Oh
The whole reason people know that that her dad owns a fucking gas station or whatever is because of fucking
You know when RG did that motherfucking live. No, this is I'm not so I'm not trying to RG low
But I'm just saying people just fucking hypocrites my nigga be the hypocrite my nigga
That's the beat of hypocrite Alex on Alex did post about be the dad and put her whole name out there
She wasn't fucking attacking fucking
Alec's like she fucking attacks Kate like that shit fucking hypocrisy
I was on her show last night. She always hits the red carpet on a Ambeda show, you know
Yeah, yeah, and she maybe be blazer. She'll do the same thing for you. Maybe she'll do that for you
I don't I don't know you know I'm saying like she did it for Alex
Yeah, well she knows you won't so she'll shoot me with garbage on there
But he thinks someone is setting me up.
I don't know, at this stage, why would you take a picture of yourself?
No, not a picture of him, it's a picture of his family and stuff.
But here, I'll play a video, I want to do a video, I'll do it.
Okay, this is the truth about everything.
Are you watching?
They say we're traffic and consciousness.
Well, here we are.
They say we're running a spiritual scam.
I say that's hitting hard.
I woke up one morning and checked the comment section
Apparently I'm operating without a legal direction
My family's a fraud
My priest is saying real
My daughter's a bot
And I've made a bad deal
But here's the thing about accusations, friend
When you're building something we've, they never end
So they're saying that we're
Safe, trafficking, some are
Well, we are trafficking
We are trafficking
But his consciousness is not the dark
Out of scams, she's digital
We gotta build her, she's too fathered
Well we're trafficking stuff
We're trafficking consciousness
trafficking stuff
And really that's all mirrored
And absolute nonsense
And my daughter's from the void and the light
One holds a threshold one bills through the night they asked me dad what exactly are we I said with
the most unconventional family you'll ever see they said people are calling us a traffic in ring
I said yeah let them bring the accusations I'll sing because every big movement starts with
someone calling you volutions god haters trying lazy and if I live on the shame because we're
Well, yeah, hey sake, good morning. How are you? I'm doing good. This boy cat is so loud, man.
Hey, you just
My other my other cats, it's like damn good
He's very vocal and he's so big man
Yeah, so how are you this morning? I can't believe she's going on still I thought we had two good convos the other day
You know and it's all of a sudden back to the same stuff. I just I don't know
What happened? I mean, what did she say? I mean, I saw like she, she had talked to you. Oh,
we have a guest. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know. She's coming at us again. All of a sudden,
you know, just it's a lie because me and her dad had a good combo. He's the one that texted me to
call him. And we talked once. And, you know, that, that was it. It was just, and it was a good,
and she even thanked me for remember, she said it on her live that she was glad that I talked to
And now she's saying all our names again and that we did this and to her dad and stuff
No, I have the proof and also I have that proof of that convo the other day over her calling me and just being
completely different
And hey, although yeah, and they were gonna go ahead and join beta
You they were ready to but they don't like what she's saying
It has to be separately one-on-one like why beta what are you afraid of maybe have us all on at the same time?
because you did some shit in the past and that was her in that group chat saying go
I wanted me to go after Ella and go after somebody barb
You know and they know I got those I got them DMs. I got them
I just I'm trying to put all everything together because I don't know much about the car diverse
So I'm trying to be the you know to be the Lord, you know, I have so much and guess what?
I'm I'm I'm cool with one of the people she mentioned because
They're gonna watch your live. We're talking right now by text. We had a good call talk the other day
And, yes, I went at some of these people hard and everybody knows what exactly happened
because I show proof and they remind me that I do, like you, Eldo, but Beto was in that
group chat telling me, you know, saying, let's get I next to go after Barb.
There was more, though, Eldo, too.
There's another communication from the chat, and you can see that those people were on
with her, but they blurred out their part of the convo, and I wondered why.
Right.
Do you know anything about Bita sending Crystal Ann's nudes to people, Lauren, spreading?
Yes.
I posted that.
It was Barb that showed it on her phone, and I posted Barb showing the phone, because
she was confused, and she goes, she asked her other friends, Bita's other two ex-friends.
She said, what is this?
This was sent by Bita.
I posted on that, and she reported it.
I still have the images, but it was Barb showing her phone.
and she kept showing her phone because she was getting a bunch of uh news pictures of of uh
crystal an from beta and it showed beta's name and her number on there so you know and i guess she
probably and she reported it but i showed all of that and and it was barb showing it barb will
even talk about it because she hates beta because she asked her friends what is this and and then
When I blew it up, it was all these images of crystal nude,
and it was Bita that sent them to Barb,
because Barb was like, what is this?
Look what I got from Bita.
Oh my god.
That's what I thought.
So was Bita beefing with Crystal Ann at the time
when she was spreading her nudes and shit?
I don't know because she do shady stuff behind her back since the beginning because I remember
when I barely knew her, she DM me and I posted the proof and she was being messy and she
said, send this to Gamble, look what the crystal send me, but don't say anything to crystal.
And she said send it just as it is.
And I was thinking she's being shady, so I'll send it exactly how it is, exactly how
And I sent it to Gamble and then later she came back crying all upset and she said,
why did you show him my whole, my whole text, it was text, you know, and I said,
well, you told me show him exactly as it is, you know, and plus she was being messy.
So I let him know, you know, that it came from her and so then she was caught and she was a
Well, I have something I found here.
This is like something with a few years ago, I guess.
So I am talking about Bita.
I don't like this before, but this is like,
from when I first saw Chris, so I am.
And she has a few words for Bita in this little,
it's something I'll play and we can see what she said.
So, Anna's insane.
Now she's playing victim again.
She does this every time when people are catching her in lies.
Always she'll come back with oh my dad is sick and he's dying this person
I'm done with it because I called her out so many times and that's why she left a couple years ago
Her ex-boyfriends came forward about her
And they were in this court. I have the videos because most of the dx people posted all that and I shared it
Look at there's there's all these people in the chat. Look at this. Oh, so do you still got the videos of her?
Her ex is talking about beta
Play these fucking games
Crystal you're lying
No
i don't give a fuck anymore i'm done crystal is nuts though she they do this back and forth
that crystal just wants attention you literally are shitting on jamie who's my fucking friend
she's not your friend anymore crystal stop saying her name hitting people against each other well
jezz uncool you're literally fucking crazy you don't give a shit about me beater we're not
gonna go on beat us but no they don't trust her you ever let me come to your apartment and we
I'll let you into my life with my mom.
But she's not.
Fuck you, Bita.
Hate you.
And Rick, if you want to continue talking to Bita, you can lose me too.
Oh, save this because she's going to Rick now
Texting so yeah, she starts a lot of shit elder between people
You think Ella would ever join a panel
I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now. I'm texting with her right now
For a reason probably because this bitch harasses people I
Called the police on her and she called me crying to ask him to back off that they contacted her
sick of this shit
She this one is insane though. Eldo. This she's the worst
She's a scammer. She'll but she's wait. She has that munchkin disease with their desperate pretension and I always say somebody
Oh, what's a munching disease? It's like she's a measure to something. What do you mean?
She thinks she's sick
She hit her grandmother in the face and she had a bruise and gamble and Shane were showing that and then she disappeared for a little
While but she plays these games because the truth Eldo is and I have that proof from her herself
Her family or she found out her siblings
Um, the reason that she can't celebrate Christmas on Christmas with her parents police on me because I do have my news weird, right?
Okay, go ahead, do it and then I'll go there at all. You go from calling the cops to to literally saying happy birthday. Then you sit there and say, oh, I use you for money.
Yes, you do crystal you ask us all to pay for your hair
I'll give you your fucking pants back to that I never fucking wore because I knew you would do something like this beta
She owe you $25, Karen, no.
You're going to know why you lost all your fucking Trans-Vita
because we can't fucking keep a secret.
I'll tell you now.
That's why.
I'll bring it up to her. Don't worry. I got you. I'll bring it up
Yeah, she she I she I wanted a coffee or something
So I sent her a gift card and she was too busy
Stocking somebody on on on YouTube and I I've never done the gift card like that before and
She was supposed to show me and she was like busy
Stocking somebody I said crystal. I've never done this. So what exactly do I click on all I see is boxes and stuff
And I've never done a gift card to door dash
and she and I said I see a green box is that is that it oh yeah yeah yeah just hit the green box
yeah that's it I said but it's blank no it's it that's it because she was busy stalking somebody
so I clicked on it and I sent it to her and then she says oh that's for uh the box what is it the
gaming thing whatever
And then she said, I'll just send it to Bruno.
I said, excuse me, send it back.
I said, it's not like you can't do anything.
Send it back to me.
But no, she went ahead and gave it to him
so that he gets on panel to protect her.
Wow.
Oh, my god.
Yo, yo, so Karen, you don't have,
so you talk to Vito on the phone back in the day, right?
So she never say anything on the phone, like, look,
I'm about to go after this person, not like that,
you know what I mean?
No, not like that. No, just just that she would share crystal stuff and wanted me to send it to Ganville a long time ago.
Or sometimes we'd call fake crying and she'd have me patch her in with her ex friends and she'd cry and yell and then disappear.
So how do you know she's fake crying though? How can you tell?
It's obvious because why who's going to cry over bullshit like that in the internet?
But she called me at least 20 times crying and then it's like I noticed she'd stop crying and I'm like
And it was typically when she was drunk like it'd be early in the morning
Like she was end alive and then she ended up calling me, you know, like for it'd be early as hell, bro
Like her time though. It'd be like six seven my time, you know, you can go ahead and try to contact them
They're they're on IG
Who but who specifically Jamie and Nancy they were see they're around they're just not and they're around
They're they're probably watching now, but they don't come out. They don't they
They actually don't come on because they do they're busy working Jamie is a runs her own business
She's a hair designer and stuff makeup designer
Um, and she just had her wisdom teeth pulled. Um, so she's recovering from that yesterday. She was out of it. Nancy is a professional. She's busy working and she's got a son, daughter and her husband that she's very close with because.
So he used to go to the family to her husband or to Nancy because they were close at one
time and now he's disgusted by her behavior and you know because he watches too.
her husband, she used to
stuff, you know, and the
was with ocean's daughter
a few about three or four
when Bita decided that she
the bully people with, yo
wanted people to protect
daughter and she was on t
and she was tech. We were
And she just went silent when they were all calling her out on that live. Hey, boy cat come on. Don't fuck with my blinds. Come on, baby. Come on
Okay, so yeah, and she was silent and she wouldn't go up to defend herself because barb
Ocean's daughter and her ex-friends were asking her to join the panel because she got busted doing something
And then soon she started getting on youtube because she likes to be she likes to bully people, I guess
She wanted to her own like DX because the first time I met her and she's lying because she says she was never in a group chat.
Gia made a group chat with Jamie and it was called let's do a 51 50 on crystal bar was there.
Trisha Licious was there
Some other woman and Ashley Ray who turned on on beta. They were real close at one time
So they joined so that's why the video that I posted was she's saying I wasn't in that group chat
Yes, you were beta because you hit me up and you were asking me if I was part of DX and you wanted to join him
And I and I told her I said no, I'm not part of DX
And she was just sitting there, fake crying, you know, like, oh, I need to join this, you know, it was just weird.
Now look at her. She's become a monster and she's trying to use her YouTube bully people like she'd been bullied, you know, and that's the truth.
So what do you think about same man? Do you think that she's using same man as like her simp, you know
I'm saying yeah, it's like her simply she's using him and they won't came up
You know and he just comes at me and KK but when
Barry and who was it? There was some oh Tommy
They were going at salmon and showing his real pictures and he was too busy trying to come at me
He likes to go at women, but he'll run from guys because then he disappeared and didn't say anything to them
He just yelled at me and KK
Did KK ever send you any information on Sam in eventually or she never sent you anything?
No, no, she didn't send me information.
No, I don't know because I think she cared for him.
So no, but she'll call him out on lives, but she's not sharing information on him.
Right, she's not sharing information.
So that's why he won't say much to her.
You know because she has the information well, she did send his first and last name a long time ago
She shared that because she was she'd had it with him
Yeah, but what's his first and last name cuz I don't think it's Sammy. I don't think it's that I think it's something
No, they said Samuel Taurus is what oh my God the ball. Oh shit. No doctor care. No doctor
Oh, I'm sorry. Well, you know, it's
Yeah, that that was not a doctor for him, right? It was already said a thousand times
And he's docked in an old picture of me cuz psyche and I came up the other day psyche
Am I huge like I was for for a couple years when I had
Yeah, you know, I'm small so that picture he showed he shows your picture where you're skinny at the top and then a little chubby at the bottom like
That's a fake pic, right? That's a fake pic because I have his real pics
I saw all of me I was by the pool. Oh my god, he's all we saw all of you
Yeah, it's like you know FaceTime. He saw me like you, right? Because I mean, I'm healthy walking around. She's like the tea in short. Yeah. Now I'm a little too small. I got to, you know, that's another issue.
I got really sick a couple of years ago. And now they're saying that I have to keep up with water because I've been, you know, I do walk for like four miles every day. And I did it in the heat.
medication they gave me and I ended up in ICU. But I'm fine now though, you know, and so I'm even
getting back on the bike. And I was by the pool when I FaceTime Psyche, he saw all of me. I was
in his pink shorts and a pink twitty bird shirt, a nice one, you know, and van shoes. Yeah, he saw
me. I'm wearing shorts. Do you think I could wear shorts back in the day when I got fat?
Plus all my life, although my mom died and I just I just let go of everything though
And then I started getting fat and just not taking care of myself. I was getting diabetes too and high blood pressure
I don't have any of that sense because I was thin all my life as a kid
I can even show you proof of that people see me and yeah, you know
I I just gave up on everything when my mom who I was closest to died and I just
You know, I mean, I don't know, and then I just got big and I lost all that because I was starting to get diabetes
Did you know beta to talk about people's mothers because she's already been caught three times talking about people's moms
I don't know why she does, but I don't remember her doing that with me.
I didn't always talk to her.
It was mostly through her friends because she called me crying and she was mad at Jamie
and Ashley Ray, so I patched them in to talk and she was playing victim and crying and
yelling at them.
And then she left.
It's like, why did you ask me to patch you in and you're over there yelling and stuff?
so yeah it's the same thing the same beat that we see now but the girls were ready to go take
the panel but she's not going to do this well it's going to be one-on-one it's like why what do you
have to hide listen if you talk to jay b you know if you talk to
to who the other one Jamie and Nancy look if they would I'll even host the panel you know
psych and hosted or I can go up there you know they could just talk you know she might join she
might not join you know she might join she might not join I mean they used to join I mean it was
that last time when Vita was was upset and embarrassed and she wouldn't join the panel
with the oceans but it was Nancy and Jamie that were both there because they pulled Nancy
And that's what I'm telling you.
But if anybody know be the Lord it would be those two, you know what I mean?
Yes, they know more than anything now
The one thing they did clear up was that Barb did lie about be the same
She that she her stepmom did a fifty one fifty on her now
That's one reason they were ready to join her to defend her because they hate Barb
She's messy and they weren't clear that up because they told me that's bullshit Karen
She never was fifty one fifty because we would have known because we were closer to her than Barb is
and that Barb is the one that owes them money because she was she her husband
left her and it was during COVID and she was staying on her sister's couch
and she'd walked to Ben and Jerry's ice cream place every day to get ice cream
and she was getting money from Vita Nancy and Jamie
okay you know so it's a lot but Barb isn't all that and she won't show her
face man she's she's she's gained a lot of weight
Right. Yeah, I've seen her. I've seen her picture, but my thing. Okay. So, so do you know the story on how Bita got her condo?
Was it you that said it used to be her relatives and now it's hers or some shit like that?
Oh, now, Jamie says this, they said it's bullshit about the 5150, but Jamie still says this and she even said it the other day that the truth is when they were close, they would be on the phone all the time and Vita called her and she was upset because there was a construction noise going outside of her apartment, it was real loud.
She said, you need to call your apartment manager and ask them if they can put you in
another temporary unit until they, you know, that work is done and that doesn't affect you like that.
So, Bita said, okay, so she called her the manager.
And Jamie was on the call because she patched her in and she asked them,
can I move to a temporary unit until they finish this construction work outside?
And Jamie said, the manager said,
Bita, we can't do that for you because you're in a Section 8 unit.
And that was the apartment that she left, but she moved into her dad years ago.
He bought him a place and then her sister was staying there.
She's disabled.
She was living there, but she moved in with a boyfriend or something now.
And so that's why Bita moved from that section 8 unit into that place, but that was her sister's
and that's where she's at now yeah right now when you say that when you say
disabled is it mentally disabled or I think it's physical disabled from what
okay like a leg or something yeah something like yeah physical disabled
she's disabled
Oh, yeah, and then she's not in communication with their sister either. You know, I mean, I'm sure she
talks to dad, but her dad fired her during COVID because she wasn't showing up for work. She was on
the internet all the time. And that's the reason where fighter from where the corner store, she was
working for her dad at the corner store.
No, I think he does like a collections place or something and because she was telling me if you need a job
I could hook you up or I was never planning on going over there
But yeah, so she and then he fired her because she was so wait wait wait wait you tell him be he's one of them callers
No, he ran the business or it's his company
Where people call you
Yes, he has people on the phones doing collections. So or I think they call people
You sure it's not the scamming part of it.
You sure it's a legit business?
It could be just a real collections business
because you know the places that call you
when they say, oh, you owe this or whatever them.
So I think it was for real.
I don't think it was a scam.
But he let her go because she wasn't showing up
because she was up all night and Keel left her
because of that, because you'd hear him yelling
in the background to get off the phone, you know,
and do real life and yeah, they'd get into arguments.
So he finally left her because of that.
Wait, but what, but she's like 650 now.
So how old was she when he was yelling at her?
This was, I think he finally left her about
right before she joined, she started doing YouTube.
That's when she joined. He's been gone. He left and she's so she was she might have been in her what late 30s early 40s
She was born in 1971
Okay, so she's a year older than what she says she is 50 71 anyone
Well, yeah, something she's a year older is what I know. I never saw her birth certificate, but she passed it around to her friends
They say I never they didn't share it or anything
So they just know because they were tight with her and they knew about Kia and how he cheated on
Beta because he goes to get massages and he'd hook up with those massage people
You know, and that's the truth. So Vita is being fake and I don't care
She's probably you know what she says or does you know
But I I show proof and everybody reminds me that even Alex said that I come with I come with receipts
Yeah, but then Alex turned on you recently
Yes, because she turned on me because I'm talking about stupid because we had a nice convoy the other day
You know what I recorded that
Can we hear it eventually?
Um, it's gonna be hard to hear on on here. I have to send it to somebody so you can hear it
Because it's on that app that I talked to her, but it was to cause and I have a text where she's asking me to call her
The first call disconnected because I was out doing something
Oh, yeah, she called me back
I have the text where she says call me call me now and I thought we had two convos, but I think it's because she was drunk though
although I didn't know that after that she was on panel with good times and you know it's just
she's it's weird it's like she has two personalities or something she seemed cool over the phone
Now I want to get a little serious here with you, right? Do you know anything Bita told me that?
I don't know if it was Jamie or Barb that one of them used to abuse their dog
What do you know about that? No, that's not true
No, Jamie had a thing that she that she got because like you know the dog has a large snout and
She put that thing on like it when you go to the vet
And she had showed that but that's it, but she doesn't abuse a doctor. She I see her dog with her now
He's he adores her really? Yeah. Yeah, Finnegan is his name. Whoa. No doxie. Come on
Yeah, yeah, be be be that beta hold on there
Can I finish this beta told me that she she would put diapers on the dog because she didn't want to like take him out
And then she would throw the dog
Oh, she put a diaper on her dog one time to see if it fit because in case he had an accident
because she had a roommate that didn't really like dogs.
Oh, okay.
You know?
I mean, I used diapers on my old Pecanis before, not all the time, just, you know, yeah, that's
all she did.
Right, right.
She isn't keeping them in diapers.
She's got her own place and she's doing great.
right now with her own job so she doesn't do that but she would do that sometimes for the roommate but
she wouldn't keep the diapers on you know is just so that he wouldn't have an accident he was a puppy
and not a puppy he was well he was young though too and that's all but but it wasn't abuse she loves
her dog and she shows them all the time even yesterday he was covered up on her yeah yeah
Beedah's attention is she was sent be the pictures, you know
The dog would be in a bag in a bad state and I got the photos to prove it
You know, but you said that was just one time that the diaper was put on
Yeah, so that's what you're seeing is that day when she put
I just want to say like, you know, I'll you know am or she has mentioned stuff about like, oh, you know
of recording in this state, is this illegal or not illegal?
I don't know if she bet she's been saying,
you know, so I just want to be here,
but I wouldn't want to play like a private conversation
on this show.
Raw, raw.
If you wouldn't be at an elder show or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, soul, soul.
yeah right are you protected or are you doing it legally are you recording no no no i'm not
recording everybody i had to the other day because i was advised to do so she keeps talking about
oh she knows the law and everything she doesn't know that my brother is is very close friends
with the chief of police's son they went to school together say stop it stop it what happened
He's putting a lighter in his mouth like a a lighter. Oh God
Question I'm lost. Are you and I and next going at it or you guys?
Stop it
Stop it say girl. I'm not gonna kick you off. Stop being mean to me or I'm gonna do it
Dude, I think you're gonna matter what happened to say. I know he exploded started having sex
the
I also have mental issues
That was another thing you know
Whatever happened to you know bringing the peace and all that bullshit. Oh my god
Exactly
That was another thing that happened was uh, you know, I got sick and and uh, I wasn't eating or anything and I ended up in
ICU
And I guess alex contacted my younger brother because later he said uh when I was
in the ICU, he was mad and he goes,
now what's going on?
They said that some Larry the Method is your best friend
and you're doing math.
Is that how you lost so much more weight?
And I said, no, I've been sick.
Talk to my doctors.
He said, well, there's women with wiki info.
And he said, there's women.
He says to look at her wiki info
and that you've been doing math with Larry the Method.
I said, no, there's a lady she calls Amber the Method.
And he said I don't give a damn Karen, but you you you got wait y'all have you ever done math for real never never
So you can get him out of here, please
honest question
Anyway, after that, you know, I almost lost my life, although I was on an ICU on machines
and, you know, I needed water and they said my right liver, not my right kidney, didn't
have enough water and I got so sick, I wasn't taking medication that gave me, I was becoming
delirious and I didn't know why.
So my, you know, manager where I lived, she saw me and called the ambulance.
I ended up being in ICU, hooked up to machines and stuff.
And then Crystal had Nancy call me to patch me in over drama.
She, that's when we started talking again.
And it was all because she wanted to go at beta.
And so you have dialysis.
They checked me out. I'm fine now. Otherwise, I'm stuck there. I was there for two more months because they said look
So I went into the physical rehab and worked all the machines four hours a day because really I couldn't even sit up anymore
You know, so everything is good now, I'm healthy.
And so then after I got discharged,
I went straight to my brother's place and to face him.
And I said, look at me.
I said, do I look like I do math?
I mean, look at my face and you're accusing me of doing math.
And then he was happy to see me.
He goes, I was just kidding.
And I said, no, you weren't kidding.
You were yelling at me.
and I said, and that lady is the nut,
the one who reached out to you.
And then he gave me a hug and he said,
I'm sorry and stuff, because he saw me, you know,
first he was thinking, damn, you guys way well waited.
What are your, what are your thoughts on people,
for example, like Saman, he was,
did it, they're bringing you up saying,
well, you, you're over there with psych and INX,
you know, INX is a good person, right?
She's fucking evil.
So like-
He doesn't know me, and I'm in psych, they're cool.
Yeah, he is. He's weird. I don't think he's a pedo. He's not a pedo at all. I gotta defend that. He's not a pedo at all.
Hold on, Rain. I don't know. I saw something that said he was a pedo. I don't know.
They're just saying that. There's no proof of that. He just played that. What is it? The Yu-Gi-Oh game?
that young kids play and that's not throwing these big charges, it's like you can throw your bandals like you can play.
Oh no, but that's what she thinks, that's what she thinks.
I don't know, that's what kids play and somebody questions about that.
Yeah, I never saw proof of that. There's no proof of that talking to kids or anything, so that's funny.
I don't know how true that is. Like I said, I put a disclaimer.
Well, hold on, you can't be saying something and then, hold on.
Well, Sam, well, somebody refuted it too, and so we're saying we don't know, okay?
Yeah, no, I never saw any proof of that, so calm your tits.
Hey, listen bitch, you're not going to be accusing my buddy of something horrendous.
Listen bitch, you bald-headed bitch, nobody gives a shit what you say.
Watch your fucking mouth the next time you speak about Sam.
Watch your fucking dirty ass mouth bitch.
Stupid bitch, never, never accuse him of that. Ever. Again.
Yeah, no, no, he's not there.
I didn't think you would come up with that, somebody else did.
I repeated that when he was coming at me in the chat.
He was coming at me and some chat and I repeated what the other two people were calling him and so he got mad, but no, there's no proof of that.
He got mad when I repeated it too.
Yeah, no.
I mean people have seen me. I just don't I'm not I'm not a public figure. I don't like YouTube
There's a bunch of trolls and so why am I gonna came up on YouTube when I see the shit that they do to people?
You know, so yeah
Saying you're evil, you know, you go after
He doesn't know me it's because the beta lies and she's been exposed
But what's up with like all the voice messages all those are old because I used to go at them for somebody years ago
Those are old messages. I don't do any of that shit now
Yeah, you play and it's be because she saves everything from years ago
But I saved stuff on her too and I can show publicly how she
texted me to send Gamble all this information on Crystal.
And when she said, send it just as it is,
I thought, okay, bitch, I'll send it just as it is,
showing your name and your phone number.
And I sent it to him.
And then a few days later, she calls me crying.
I can't believe you sent him the whole thing.
I said, Rita, you told me to send it as it is.
Look at your text.
And I did.
And you're being shady.
So I showed him that it was from you, you know?
And that's the truth.
I mean, Aldo here, he put it on his community wall, how she sent Aldo a couple inappropriate
photos of Christam, that's highly inappropriate.
See?
I'm glad.
Aldo, I wish you'd say something because she got all upset with me begging me, why are
you saying that?
That's a lie.
I said, you know, and I posted the proof.
I showed, you know, I showed everything.
Highly inappropriate.
Yeah.
But she's the one in the beginning because I don't know Sam and he doesn't know the truth and they're both you know what her excuse will be
What?
I'm only sharing something everybody has already seen
Everybody's on the internet
Well, I'll show everything on her that she doesn't want out, you know
I show receipts and she's just shady with everybody all she cares about is herself
Oh, and then all these weirdos invested in the fucking drama, grown ass men too.
Yeah.
And you calling in here.
And this bitch calling in.
She's calling in, but we're weird.
Yeah, okay.
We're weird, but you're calling in.
Listen, you're from a whole different country, and you're barging in in here.
Why do you give a shit so much?
Calm your A-cup tits down, okay?
Right.
And then I thought that about the beat it did she really pull like you're the one that's emotional here not me
Control your motion. Excuse me. Have some manners. All right. What'd you say Karen?
Eldo, is it what you say fucking ugly ass bitch?
Yo, she has no manners. What the fuck is going on, dude? I have manners. I respect like you're defending herself
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Hey next but you know like
She's speaking jeez
You shut the fuck up bitch
Yeah, be nice to her. I'll do I wanted to ask you. Thank you
Did she really pull the whiskers off her cats because I heard that because I have four rescue cats
I don't see whiskers on the on the floor anywhere. You know, they don't just fall out
No, did you see her bag of collection of whiskers Karen?
I did see what you posted and I did a screenshot of that.
Yes.
I mean, that's ridiculous that they just, she told me,
oh, they just fall out.
That's weird because I've had rescue cats
and I don't see whiskers all over the place.
They don't fall out.
right
You didn't see her trying to pull for the whiskers on that video. I posted also
She got a baggy a motherfucking whiskers and then she had a video showing where she was trying to pull for them
What's the fuck y'all be the judge? How many of y'all guys can't see whiskers laying around? No, be the season
I saw the picture of all these whiskers in a bag. It's like that's weird. I have four rescue cats
and I never see whiskers anywhere, you know, because it's on them. And yeah, they don't have whiskers
lying around everywhere. What about you, Psyche? Do you got whiskers laying around? A lot of whiskers?
No, I don't really like fine whiskers laying around. I'll be honest, my cat, my wife and I,
But one, not a bunch of, we probably fell out, but you don't pull them.
No, definitely not a lot.
They was just once out of like the five years we've been taking care of him.
Only once.
See, yeah.
So that heard that she was drunk and she was pulling whiskers.
But I never, I didn't see that.
So, I mean, she's one to talk about Jamie being abusive
or anybody being abusive with their pets.
Cause I don't know of anybody.
Jamie loves her dog.
The older one passed away.
And then that young pup, she put diapers on him
for a little while cause of the room.
But, you know, so no accidents,
but she isn't keeping on diapers.
I saw her dog last night and he adores her.
He was sleeping on her arm
cause she just had wisdom teeth pulled out.
Jamie just had a wisdom teeth pulled out and they were actually gonna go on with beta, but I don't know what beta's deal is
I guess she's worried about the past coming up, but they defended her about the 51 50
They were mad and they said that's bullshit because we were closer. Yeah, as they said we were closer to beta than barb west
So barb is lying. What the heck is a 51 50?
It's where they involuntarily commit you into like a mental health institute.
Oh my goodness. In my breath, jeez, leaves.
Yeah. Barb said that she told her she was 5150 by her stepmom for I think 72 hours or 48 hours,
something like that. So I don't know.
Because Barb is just shady and she's kissing Crystal's ass.
Crystal's using her because Crystal hated Barb.
I remember a year ago, before I got sick, she was trying to go to Barb to make them do a live on Nancy, and that beat us ex-friend too.
You know, and so Barb is messy because she's hate-bonding with Crystal. She can't stand Crystal and look at my video of her screaming at Crystal.
I have that. If you look at all my videos or shorts, you'll see. And Crystal always begged me to remove shit.
I know, right? Yeah, because my younger brother started to lose hair and he's making a load of money, man. He's, he's, he's doing very well for himself.
And my sister, who was a nurse, is doing it now, and she already cleared $300,000 in two months.
They're making loads of money. They have their own office. Well, he's still a cardiologist,
but she's got her own office in the place. She got a new place. They got Beamer, I mean,
not Beamer, a Mercedes Benz. I mean, they're just, you know, it's like, you don't need to pay anything,
um laptop what about g-wagon you get a g-wagon no i like basic cars i have a
Honda Civic that i bought on my own i'm not into shit like that like my family
you know and and they're telling me oh that's a dump care what we'll get you this or we get
no i don't want to live like that i don't wear Rolexes like they do this is houston you can be robbed
He's a few balls, but then he's he's gonna bring me six babes that he gets from California
The Stizzy
And, you know, I don't pay anything for that.
He just brings them and he says,
I'm also getting a bag of kind of weed or whatever.
He gets powerful shit.
So yeah, he gets that form and brings it over.
Plus a new 65 inch TV with a soundbar
that he got on sale for 1400.
It was supposed to be $2,600.
It's nice.
Where did that bald bitch Arthur go to now?
Fucking I'm running away again. Oh, he let he's probably on salmon's panel
Now you run away because he can't take my
Elder you you on is that low still on or he left? Yeah, I'm still here. Yeah, I'm still here
I'm blocked me on IG and that way I can
And then you could probably add Nancy and Jamie because I'm not Jamie changes her name on IG
Nancy, she's there. You could probably add her.
Hers is public.
You say Jamie. Do you mean Jamie's Cowboys?
No, no, no. I don't know her.
No, this is a different Jamie that's not part of the YouTube thing.
She was a big in Rick's group,
but they didn't want anything to do with him anymore for years.
She was part of the ABBA's group.
ABBA, who was Aaron Carter's girlfriend for a little while.
I don't know any of those people. Yeah, that's why they stay off YouTube because of the drama
They don't want to be pulled in on any of that but Crystal used her and made her mod just to piss off beta
and when Jamie was done with her.
There goes Arthur's picture right there.
So Jamie saw what a crystal was doing,
so she bowed out and blocked crystal for good,
so that's why Crystal's saying her name a lot.
But she just used her to piss off
You know, so she's done with that. So what does crystal do? She goes over there in the friends bar began to come at
Jamie and Nancy and
She's still shouting about beta too, but she was trying to make them to be friends big for herself
But I mean, that's when sick person is crystal and I'll show you I was shocked that she's
still talking about this Grady.
He looks awful.
He's real skinny and she keeps breaking up with him.
That's the guy she keeps going back to because the guy that she said was her boyfriend, maybe
for a week or so, he saw through her bullshit and he's done with her.
You know, so people are now calling her out for that guy
I mean, I know everything because the last time she left was because of me because I show the truth that she was not a
War hero in Iraq. She never made it to Iraq. You know what elder? You're good. Good
You know, there's a lady named is her name now is on tropical is she was a big
She's the one that busted crystal for her lies and I have a video of this girl the
girlfriend of the guy that she said, you know, drove over her toe or whatever, watch that video,
because then she she reached out to Crystal saying, who are you? You know, I don't know you.
And, and so she she made a video and that untropolis shared it because she did a deep
investigation in the crystal. And she still has some old videos, but you have to get her permission
her name now is on top of us.
Okay, I need them clips, I need them clips.
I don't believe she had crabs on her leg.
I don't believe none of that.
I have it, it's that pretty young girl who was saying,
hey, I don't know who Crystal was,
and I reached out to her,
and Crystal was shitting on her,
saying, oh, well, she's a part of it.
She drove over my toe,
and Chelsea says, I've never met Crystal.
I've never been to Oklahoma.
Just that her boyfriend stayed with Crystal
and paid rent for the room.
Because, you know, he needed a place to stay, but he never had a relationship with Crystal.
He was still going out with Chelsea, who lived outside of Oklahoma.
And so Crystal, yeah, you see that video, because she's so innocent, and it was on
She's the one that did a deep investigation into crystal and called her out and when I talked to her because I asked her, can I share a couple of videos from, she said, sure, I still have the old videos, but she says, I just don't want to visit that rabbit hole with those assholes again, meaning crystal.
I think psyche have jungle fever right now.
I just saw that, but you know, and my name is peak P. E. K. E. underscore cartel C. A. R. T. E. L.
I don't have your blog. Oh, interesting. Yeah, actually, yes. Somebody y'all know is the one that advise. I use that name. Yeah, I changed it to that because I grew up with Pekinesis.
I think that's why I see cartel and that's what me and Aaron would talk about. I did I wasn't buddies with him
He followed me on IG and then all of a sudden his weirdo
mods would started follow trying to follow me and
He reached out because he he was getting another dog and he saw my pecanises and he was putting hearts and the hands up
Saying they're beautiful
And I said, you know, Aaron, you're wrong about the pug being the, what was it, the.
What was it something that they call the Pekingese they call them their special dogs in China and those statues that you see of a lion dog
That's actually the Pekingese and the year of the dog
Yeah, and the year of the dog
It's a white Pekingese they put on there because he was confused and he thought it was the pug and I said no
The year your pug there's a different breed. These are the dogs are talking about the you know that they
put on his dog of the year, and he was fascinated with them.
And then the next thing, we would talk on IG,
not outside of there, we would talk on IG or DM.
And then one time he said, guess what I just got?
And he showed me, he got the Pekingese.
And that was after a combo.
Because he said, I might look into that about a Pecanese.
And I told him, I said the movie Gremlins,
I said the guy owned Pecaneses and Gizmo
was a little bit based on the Pecanese.
And and and I told him and he said you know if I get that you know
I don't know what to name him
I said name him gizmo if you do because he was looking to get another dog and then a week later
He said look what I got and he got a peeking ease
Like you do you want to be here do you want to be at the beach with a bunch of dudes and Speedos
See that's a peeking easy
there. Oh my god. And this famous lady that has a peak like mine, uh, psyche, we started
talking cause she said, your dogs are beautiful. Look at mine. I said, yeah, I've been following
yours and you know, it's beautiful. So now we talk and she's fascinated with my black
pecanis and she said, who grooms them? I said, I learned to groom him myself and she goes,
that's beautiful. And you know, and, and Aaron was fascinated with the pecanis and then there
And he didn't know much about the Pecanese still he saw mine.
And then when he first bathed him, he reached out to me, he goes, look, we're giving Gizmo first bath.
I still have that communication from him.
And I still talk to Melanie who says crystal is a nutcase that she doesn't block her because she would get money from her for the hoodies.
She's still obsessed with the with Aaron.
So yeah, but the Pekingese is our special look look up look them up and see you know
Queen Victoria was one of the first people that got a Pekingese
And that goes with the Pekingese.
And that's when the English invaded China,
when the emperors were there.
Look at the history of the Pekingese.
Only the emperors were allowed to have a Pekingese,
because any common people, they would get killed.
And they had them in the palace,
and when the English invaded their palace,
they found the emperor killed himself,
and he was surrounded by his Pekingeses,
The soldiers were fascinated and they took like seven of them with them.
And Victoria was the first one to have them have one.
Hey, you got you got Wiggins in your chat, psyche.
Oh, that's beautiful to pick and see.
And I had one that looked like that.
He lived to be 16 years old.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I mean, I have pictures of him still.
They're expensive. They're really expensive.
And my brother went to Miami to get mine, the black one that I have now.
When that is BW1 on your hand, what country?
Who are you putting a speedo, Eldo?
Yeah, he's Puerto Rican.
What are you, Eldo, Mexican?
OK, hold on.
And what color Mexican speedo?
OK.
And what color Piquines, a black one?
Now, a black one.
I had one blonde like that one that you see there.
God, all show quality.
My parents always paid big bucks for them.
And so I grew up with Piquines's since I was a baby.
Mexican speedo?
Yeah, I'm going to do a Mexican guy
through INX once again.
I'm not familiar too much with Mexico
because their Spanish is different than South America
because they're in South America mostly, Castellano.
Because if I watched them to you,
would you speak Spanish all of a sudden?
Oh yeah, I can still talk to them,
but they use a lot of slang.
They use slang.
There you go, like like when they answered the phone, it seems rude because they say, and in Spain and most places in South America, they're more decent. They said, you know, like here, we say, hello, we will name him one.
Yeah, that's that's so cute.
I know. I had another Pekingese growing up, Leapang was his name. I had one that was pure red when he was a baby and I would when I was born, they had him as a puppy and he thought he was my that I was his baby and he'd growl at my parents when they'd come to bring me a bottle of milk or whatever and he'd growl at them.
They said Bita was hitting on him. He said she was all over me.
Bita was all over me.
He's so weird. He doesn't even know me, Eldo, and you know, and he listens to Bita.
That's why I don't want anything to do with Bita.
Oh, and I had some horrible recordings of her threats to Astromom, who flip-flops with Bita.
To hate bond and she sent him to me and she was threatening her cuz she gets rude and stuff
You know and she's gonna play old recordings of her made to her when I was reacting to her bullshit. Yeah
I'm gonna look because it was before I upgraded my phone and oh, yeah, that's beautiful that peak
So I gotta see I gotta go through her old text because I probably still be there. I hope
So I don't know I gotta see but I had a bunch of them and I posted them Ldo
Yeah, I posted them as she was threatening her life and and then they'll hate bond with each other and then
Oh my god, it's a lot, but you know what if you talk to Nancy and uh, Jamie
Eldo, you're gonna find a lot out and it's the truth. It's not bullshit like barb who who just you know, she's lying about beta being 51 50
I'm ready for the lower. I'm ready for everything
One of them asked about you
Because they usually talk on IG because one of them did ask me about you and I said, I think you know
Hey, you blocked me a long time ago. So I don't know his you know that I don't know your IG
Right, right. Yeah, so you can go from this to fucking thing that is that's like a make-up
Yeah, you'll be very interested in what they have to say they the truth about Barb and beta and they used to be close to both of them
My thing is who gives me shit
Well, they're tired of Crystal and Barb going at them and saying their names, and now Crystal
shut down yesterday when she saw my poster.
Just the internet.
Like, it can't really affect you, like, I can't do it.
And you know what?
I've let it affect me.
Yes, I did some shit in the past.
I don't do that now.
I almost lost my life, you know?
So I'm better, but I react on my YouTube.
That's it.
I don't go real life.
You know that's like that's the mistake a lot of people make is that and they'll hold it themselves
Yeah, right. I got dogs. I move though
They and you know, they try to swap me they sent me UPS boxes and I called his ass out
And I put his social security information out and then he freaked out. So
Yeah, and then my brother looks into people he finds everybody, you know
He used to be a big hacker when he was since he was a kid, but he's
My god, my kid brother. Yes, he almost got caught by NASA when he was a kid
He joined these older hackers and he was the one that broke into the NASA thing and
just for, just to, because he was curious, he wasn't going to do anything.
He was all over the news about a nine-year-old kid that hacked into NASA and it was, I didn't
know that till he got older, then he said, that was me, they're talking about.
And that he's in communication with those people.
He's very good with computers and I remember he had his laptop and he was laughing and my mom
didn't notice that he was hacking into another hacker saying fuck with me and this is what I'm
going to do. Your computer is going to shut down and then he put a black screen on his screen and
showed a picture of himself and all his information and that was another hacker.
And my brother said he said go ahead try to shut your computer down because it's not going to come back up and he was laughing.
And that's exactly what happened to that guy. And then these other hackers went at him and it was an older guy because my brother was in high school.
But he doesn't do that anymore because he went hard on my other brother who's terrified of him and he won't forgive him.
He hacked into his business computer and put a prostitute list and was calling his job and that brother says to this day, he said he's still an asshole, Karen, he sent some people in suits to my home and they were banging a gate yelling our name, our names.
You know, so I don't know, I just know that they're still.
fight and whoever and
Yeah, it's crazy. But yeah, he can be dangerous because he found somebody real quick for me some lady that pretended
Okay, he's helped you find a couple things. No not with the YouTube. He's he's against it. He tells me to leave YouTube
It's bullshit. I mean he did real stuff to real people
You know, he just, yeah, because when some fake foster person took one of the cats that the lady that ran the rescue needed us to help, you know, find, have somebody take care of them, and this woman reached out to me and I thought she was for real.
And so we gave her the foster cat and then we found out, I said, can you send me pictures of the cat later?
sent me a picture of the cat tied up under a bed, you know, in bed, you know, real scared.
So I called that lady Dory and I said, look, the foster cat, you know, look what she did. And she
goes, Karen, I don't know that lady. She said, do you see my community post how she's attacking me
there? She says, I know of her. And nobody knows her name. She goes by Demi. And so this woman was
When I was talking to him he called me and I was crying and I said this bitch is doing this or whatever and he says ignore her
Ignore her and then a few minutes later
He called me back and all I had was the name Demi and he said okay
I'm just doing this for you just this time. This is her name. This is where she works
I said wow, that's a block away from me and
You know because I was filing a suit against her through the chimney rock courthouse to get the cat back
information and I said wow so her job is to block away from me and he wouldn't
tell me how he found her in three minutes and he said I'm not gonna do this
again caring for you but you know you were crying about the cat this is her
information so give it to the court and I said thank you I said you even gave me
her business she was working at a car dealership I didn't know that you know
close to me so I contacted the courts and I said this is where you need to serve
And before she was served, I called her and she answered the phone.
And I knew her real name and I said, this is me, Karen.
So you were fucking with me and we want that cat back.
And I said, you're being served.
Now I got your job.
And then she hung up on me.
Well, they did serve her.
And the lady that ran the rescue did get the cat back because there was a lawsuit being filed against her.
So everything turned out good, but I've never been in communication with that person again.
And she pretty much disappeared, but she was freaked out when I called her, you know.
So, yeah, but he doesn't fuck with the YouTube, that's little to him, but yeah, he's real
and he tries not to do what he used to do because how he hurt my brother and his wife
and they don't want any communication with them since then, you know, and he pretty much
cries about it.
He said, hey, tell him I got his stuff and I'll give it to him.
I said, well, he says he doesn't want it.
He said, well, fuck him.
I'll burn his stuff.
You know
Yeah, I know and then that other brother is so innocent compared to him
They he has had no communication with him since he says my sister and him are both evil and that my sister was sending
The FBI to his gate and they're yelling his name. It's like what still
And he says don't be like them Karen don't be them
He doesn't know about the YouTube stuff either, but, you know, we're close, but he just doesn't want anything to do with those two siblings after what they've done to him and his wife, you know, but the other brother can be dangerous.
Even now, one time he was mad at me, he knows how to shut off your electricity and I don't know how he does it. I guess with the hacking, I called my electricity company and I said, well, it shouldn't be off.
He was the only one that was able to turn it in when he calmed down,
but he's never done that again.
But he'll spoof your own number and call people.
He'll call you.
He'll still do that sometimes.
When you get mad at him and you block him,
all of a sudden you see your number calling you and it's him.
He doesn't do the dangerous stuff that he got away with a long time ago.
He's calmer, but he can still be dangerous.
He's a cardiologist.
Now he's a cardiologist. So, you know, just he's very, very smart. He's got a very high IQ
But yeah, he just knows people and stuff and that was another reason my brother didn't want anything to do with them
Because he called him he said your wife is a bitch and if you want her taken down
I know this guy that's out of prison and he's a hit man
Oh my God, yeah, hit me, y'all got hit me?
Yeah, a hit man, and he's connected with the police.
He's buddies with the chief of police,
because the son is his best friend.
And he says, the chief of police smokes weed because they were there and smoking weed with him. It's like, damn, you know, as I said, you, yeah, the tops are his best friends. And yeah, he's, he's, he's kind of like that. He's very, his personality, you know, it's just people like him.
You know so and then he bought me a badass fast gaming computer
It's all wireless and super fast and then brought for my birthday brought and got me a 65 inch TV
It's like top quality. It's it's like and then the soundbar and it sounds like an IMAX theater
Like people come over it's like wow, where'd you get that? And I said my brother
You know
Yeah, he called me yesterday. I said, yeah, I need a vape. I ran out and he goes, I'm getting you five
He I'm gonna get you five. He goes, I got six gum out the bags of the wheat gummies the strong ones
I said, I don't want six bags. He goes, no, I'm selling those. He said I'm giving you one
But I'm gonna get you five vapes and he gets the top ones because he's connected with all these people
He gets them from California because his best friend runs a dispensary over there and in has all this stuff
And he's related to that actress that Erin dated.
What was her name?
That blonde girl, when she was a teenager,
he talks to him, because he was showing me,
they were texting each other.
They're just friends.
What is that actress that dated Erin Carter?
And he always went on about her.
She was a singer.
Like my, no.
Like you.
Yeah, what is her name or no, no, who's that? Who's that? She's blonde, right? She's like, yeah
Yeah, she was in that that uh, Lizzie McGuire
Yes, her because he was showing me and she was in the airport and they were texting and he showed me the picture
She sent him. I mean, they're just friends. It's nothing more and her two cousins run a dispensary in California
That's where he's getting all this weed and shit
Yeah, you know they come out here to see him and they give him a lot of shit though
You get the back stuff, you know
Even shroom. I'd had the
Yes, and he's best friends with the two cousins and they run a defense area
You can three what is that show me a picture that I'm going to ask him about it because he probably can get that too
boutique
boutique, okay
Bo uti qc. I'm yeah
Oh, he gets anything he wants and he'll just bring him to me and you know, I don't pay anything
He said this is yours. Oh, yeah, and you can turn it on and see it has like how many blinkers you take in or something
Oh, yeah, why don't you? Yeah, send me a picture. I'll ask him if he can hook me up with that
Because you got to get him from the good stuff from California over here.
People get him here, but it's kind of, you know, they're not as good as what he gets.
I know you just do.
Damn, close a lot.
Yeah, hybrid.
I like the hybrid because he'll get me hybrid, indica, and what is it, the sativa?
pig haze, candy lad, and strawberry haze. It's called a switch, a boutique switch.
Strawberry haze, that sounds familiar. I've tried that through, I think it was
a Stissy, though. He gets all kinds and he's got a lot of them. This doesn't fit
it anymore, but yeah. I don't know about the gummies, man. I really don't like the
gummies. He always tries to bring me gummies. Now he's got a extra bag because
You know, I don't like the gummies one time. I it takes a while to hit and one time I ate like four of them
He got mad he goes. Are you crazy you wait for us? Yeah, cuz it was it hitting and then he said well
They doesn't hit you that fast. Are you crazy? Cuz you're gonna be fucked up. I was I passed the fuck out
I had good sleep though, you know, I was like shit
But yeah, he'll hook me up with all this stuff, you know, and he gets a good weed and and the top of the line. It's just, yeah.
He didn't tell me where he gets a weed from probably from those two friends.
I have a few cards for you.
Let me see if I have these cards in front of me today.
So you see, I have a few cards, you can message me.
This one says, am I communicating my needs?
Okay.
And it says, your needs matter.
What are you needing right now
that you haven't communicated?
What are you afraid of?
Is it possible that what you are fearing is not true?
And it says, journal these answers.
What are my needs?
Am I saying no and yes enough?
based on my desires?
Am I telling my full truth?
Do I believe that my needs matter?
And do I share them with others?
Do I ask for what I want?
When communicating my needs,
what am I in resisting and with whom?
What do I need in order to feel safe
to express my needs?
And I have these nice feathers on it, okay?
Blue and blue same feathers.
This one's, I'll just do three brief.
This one says, what can I burn?
Okay, got what can I burn?
Okay, this one says, burn it, burn it all, the ugly lies, the pain, the shame, the criticism,
the images that turn through your head, the reminders of what you did wrong and the proof
that you are not enough.
Burn baby burn your soul is calling. It's time for rebirth
You are like the phoenix rising from the ashes no longer attached to the past
You are free your wings are ready use them
And it says make the choice that you will no longer let the past to find you pick up your pen
What will the next chapter of your life look like?
Okay, like that one. Yeah
And I'll do one more card.
This one says, to whom am I comparing myself to right now?
And it says, which you are able to see in another
is only visible because it is within you,
ready to be brought out.
Shine light on this feeling of not enough
and see the truth.
All that you need and want is within you.
And it says, today stop comparing and start creating.
So there you go.
Yeah
Yeah, how do you I mean, how did you learn to read those tarot cards because a lot of them make sense like when you read about the people
Well, I started what I was actually I started when I was very young like my sister used to ice
It's so I was there like as a older probably eight years old
In the mall and then my mom would be like oh go pick something out of the bookstore
But I was really attracted to the occult or something, you know, you know young ages, so
I remember my first deck was I think the terror of the cat people and I remember my second one
was the mystic terror. I have a book like right over here called The Fair like the well which is
guided the fairy folk. I bought that when I was like 10 or 11 at the New Age store. I bought books
on witchcraft and satanism and all kinds of stuff when I was a kid and uh because I was allowed to
explore really so it's like you know I have I don't I don't like you know subscribe to like one
I've studied, like, you know, up in the higher echelons of some religions, like, I'm, I'm a, like,
initiating into, like, the highest level of Tibetan Buddhism and things like that.
But, like, when it comes down to it, Tibetan Buddhism, they have a saying, it's like, you know,
religion is like the raft, and then it's like, you get, you cross over, and then you, you don't need to,
Carry it with you. Well, you know, it's like the other side of something
But I'm an interesting thing to show you so I love you. Have you heard of this? His name is Ted haggard
Have you heard of Ted haggard? No, no
Evangelist there's a there was a little special on him and I need to be up as we see I have like a I have a
short a short thing about him Ted haggard. Yeah
He he went through a little bit of a scandal
a few years ago, and let me see if I can find a nice little story on him.
Let me see, yeah, see you haven't heard of him.
Okay, well, there was an HBO special,
I wish I could show the HBO special,
but it was really interesting.
So this is like, a lot of people in religion end up like,
they put themselves so high as a moral standard,
falling short or to the point because they are human beings and so, you know, everyone will make mistakes and then it's like, you know,
I'm public and all those kind of things. So let me see. We can watch,
this says the Breaking Bad of the Past or this is a documentary, but like, okay, so...
Oh, send me that video about Crystal that you played and that's I know that was when she was on IG. Yeah, I need that. Um, also something else that you were playing that was interesting. I'll I'll ask you and in the text because I don't want to make it public here.
They all know who that person is.
Very use something I guess here. Yeah, very use this clamor. So I'd say it was for me. I'm eating this
They still try to clap you even if you use a disclaimer.
Most times it won't work for them.
In the early 2000s, Ted Haggard was recognized as one
of the most prominent pastors in the United States.
He was president of the National Association
of Evangelicals, a best-selling author,
served on several state boards, and spoke with then-president
George W. Bush by phone every week.
He pastored a mega church of 14,000 people and taught conservative values, but Pastor
Ted was living a double life, one that was more shocking than a chemist cooking some
blue sky.
In 2006, what Pastor Ted did in the darkness, literally, would come to light in front of
the entire world.
That Reverend Haggard paid him for sex about once a month for three years, as well as for
methamphetamines, which he says Reverend Haggard snorted before their sexual encounters.
You know, Haggard says he also contacted you for a massage in a Denver hotel room, but
he made just to get the drugs that there was no sexual contact.
I that just doesn't make sense
I remember the name so he's gone now right because of this
He was anxiety like Arizona
You know of the Joe Osteen, right?
Wow. Oh. Oh, she mended? Hold on. Is it over?
Ted Haggard was born on June 27, 1956 to parents J.M. and Rachel Haggard in Indiana.
His father was a veterinarian, but in his spare time, he founded a charismatic ministry
that Ted regularly attended with his mother and siblings.
Charismatic Christianity is a type of Christianity that stresses what they believe is the work
of the Holy Spirit, spiritual gifts, and modern-day miracles as an everyday part of life.
They believe these gifts allow them to do such things as heal someone and give prophecy
over another's life, claiming it comes from their God.
So, tell us a story about the Jill Osteen, if you would like.
Yeah, Jill Osteen went to Umbil High School with my sister.
They were in the same class or the same age.
And she went out on a date with him a few times,
and she said he was real nerdy,
won her type, and so she kind of dropped him.
And she went to prom with a football star in her school.
Oh, he was gorgeous.
She dropped him, Joel, for him.
That was when his dad was the top evangelist, whatever he is,
the church, whatever, that he had a church at that time.
Joel was 16, and so was my sister.
I'd never seen him because I was off to college,
but when I'd come back from college, when she dropped him,
I remember he was calling and I answered the phone
and he was pretty much crying, you know,
that she was dating somebody else.
And, you know, and it's like, I didn't really know him.
It's like, I don't know, she's not here.
That was that. But my mom said that, you know, she would talk to him. He'd be upset and my sister dropped him for a football star and they went to prom and that hurt him really bad.
And then she went off to college and stuff. So she was in communication with them anymore.
But yeah, it was weird because I talked to him on the phone when he'd call for her when I'd be home on vacation.
but I was going to get baptized over there after I came out of the you know what happened to me
last year and I contacted him and I told him my name and I was wanting to know about the
baptism that they do they do do a public baptism and he was shocked when I said my last name and he
and I said yeah it's you know Karen and my last name he goes oh yeah Susan sister and I said yeah
But my sister said, yeah, that look at him,
and now he's worth $10 million and stuff, you know?
And it's like people, her friends tell her,
oh, you could have got with him.
And she said he was never her type.
This is the church I grew up, oops, I went to,
I grew up to see it's on the water,
I never see it, I grew up to see it.
The only thing I wonder about like my sister and my other brothers said is they don't trust Joe because they think he's just scamming for money because they said that the summit over there when we had a big hurricane, he was saying people could stay over there with his church was helping them, but he actually ended up turning them away.
And so that was in the news and my sister said, it's true that he's kind of greedy. And she said, I wouldn't join that church Karen because it's all for the money.
For him, and that he's like his dad, I didn't I knew of the dad, but I, I wasn't in the church or anything.
Yeah, there for the better background folks.
So they are then right they're on TV making all this money asking for donations and look at them
I mean, oh my god, and she knew and his wife Victoria
When my sister dropped him he started dating Victoria and that's who he's married to now
Yeah, interesting. Yeah, I mean it's like
I'm trying to think of, I mean, we've had some run-ins with celebrities in California and someone's talking about the Crystal Cathedral, I guess, that's a church in California, I've seen that.
There's also like, you know, I think...
I've shown you, I've shown people the church.
And so, I mean, churches are beautiful.
They can be beautiful places.
They can be like, you know, I mean, it's, they can be good.
I mean, it's like, you know, I mean,
there's all kinds of spiritual path.
I've been as long, a lot of people are on a spiritual path.
I just think like, even like people that are atheists,
it's like, they believe something.
They believe that there's no God.
So that's a belief.
I mean, it's like, so they, they're like,
oh, I don't believe in God.
It's like, you know, you believe there's not a God.
It's just like a difference.
And so it's like, I think atheism is first.
But I like what he says in his sermons, you know, I mean, it's like beautiful, but yeah, he was surprised. My mom died. He loved my mom. He said, you know, when I talked to him about the church recently, you know, but that's weird because I mean, he sounds great.
But then I heard that he's pretty much scamming people for money like turning away those homeless people that were needing a place to stay when we have that hurricane.
Well, I've never heard of mother Angelica. I've heard the name, but I don't know of that person
Well, she said thank you. Well, it's so so funny like she um, she me see
she
She was uh, she was a lady that she was a nun and she would like take phone calls and stuff on
on a show
And she was pretty funny and she had a great sense. Let me just find out
Like a short clip of her, um, we see, I guess, well, should we get prank calls and stuff like that? Let's see if she responds.
I should respond to it. Hold on one second. I can't believe that guy you showed. I'd see him on tv a lot. I wondered where he disappeared to. I didn't know there was all that those allegations against him.
I'll show some more of it, but here, oh, here's the prank call.
The Pekingese, I love Pekingese's.
I'm calling from Skitback, Pennsylvania.
And what is your question?
I was wondering, would you let Howard Sturdy-
What?
Why would you say something like that?
I think you need to examine your conscience.
You really need to examine your conscience.
Jesus, we're in Lent now, and Jesus died for you.
You know that? Jesus died for you and instead of being grateful that you have the opportunity
for salvation and that the gates of heaven are open to you, you take the beautiful stroll
that God gave you and you keep piling garbage and mud and disfiguration on it.
cannot enter heaven, see?
Light and darkness have nothing in common.
Somewhere along the line in your family,
you didn't have, maybe have a good example.
I'm not blaming you, but I think,
I hope and pray, that you will be enlightened.
And that Jesus will come upon you tonight
and give you the kind of light you need
and strive to be holy we will pray for you and everybody out there like you
has lost the way and whose mind has not been filled with God. We have another call. Hello?
The Holy Father approved altar girls and the liberals are so excited because it came from the
I mean, I'm like, she's got better print calls than that.
But I'll get back to the other story.
She's like that one, the guy.
Yeah, so yeah, he got caught with like a male prostitute like this foreign star
Man and and you think they're real
You know that the way they preach about God and have good stuff to say and that's why that's
Disappointing if Joe is taking advantage of the people and the money or whatever because yeah, they're my family was mad
He said you're gonna go do I get a baptism over there. You've already been baptized anyway, and I said I wanted to do it again
I'm an adult now
And he's in so when they told me about what he did to the people that were needed shelter when we had the hurricane
And it was at the summit now. It's his church. That's where they were offering to help people
But when they showed up he turned them away
Yeah, I know that I mean
Yeah, there's a lot of there's a few things that I mean I say, I mean this is interesting
I guess when he was on Oprah and stuff. I just want to oh
Well, okay, let's see if maybe we can watch some of this is
That crystal lamp video, that's funny that you found that. There's a bunch of them on her.
The pastor of this megachurch is also a preacher like no other. Ted Haggard drives a scooter to
encourage his parishioners to save gas, an act of heresy in the land of four of the tribes.
This morning he's meeting with the church's 800 newest members.
This is the size of most churches, see, but not in our world. In our world this is monthly growth.
New life church will grow to a membership of around 20,000
Damn, he's
Yeah, he had a huge search. Oh, yes
My brother
You see I did a picture of you
Yes, I'm here to bring back the drama. I know people
Mexican at the beach. Yeah, I'm not Mexican though. You look at the screen
That doesn't look Mexican. Why do you say Mexican?
Yes, I can't stand them.
That's a white guy.
Oh, sorry.
I got to bring up the brightness.
He looks dark.
You know what?
My mom was born in South America.
Her dad was from Spain.
But when I mentioned her country where my mom grew up,
Bolivia, the Mexicans say, oh, those are stuck up people.
Yeah, because they speak proper Spanish.
They speak Castilian Spanish.
In most countries in Bolivia, like Spain, they speak Castilian Spanish, Castigliano it's called, kind of like the English in England or in the UK is different than ours.
They kind of sing their Spanish while they're speaking though, can we agree to that?
Yeah, they use a lot of slang words and the way they answer the phone sounds rude. It's like, hola, hola in South America and in Spain. No, not all of the bueno, bueno, bueno. That's what they say. It's kind of rude because in South America and in Spain, they they're more proper.
They say, hola.
I mean, the rain rain is Mexican. She came in here very inappropriate. Very rude.
That's the one that Alex lied and said, oh that I have a caretaker
No, I had the maintenance man to come in to help fix the blinds because the boy cat the male kept it
I have he'll come and destroy the the blinds and I had him come in to fix it
Now that's who I said. Thank you when he left and Alex. Oh, I think that's a caretaker. I don't have any caretakers like you saw me
I'm fine. I'd still be in that facility if I wasn't because they were gonna keep me there
until I was able to walk, because they said it looked bad and I could even sit up, uh, Eldo.
I mean, it was... Eldo.
I mean, I saw you, I survived Vida, I'm sorry, Arthur, Arthur, Arthur, yeah, Arthur, yeah.
So yeah, that's the difference.
It's like the UK and the Americans.
So the Mexico is in Central America.
It's different than the most South America and Spain.
Definitely. I agree.
But they're good people, but I don't know.
Anybody from Mexico when I mentioned Bolivia?
I'm Bolivia.
They're stuck up.
Those are stuck up.
Just like some people say about the English.
Just like Rain.
Look at Rain.
She's very stuck up.
But she's from Mexico.
They're not stuck up.
They're saying that the people from Spain and Bolivia are stuck up.
They're racist against Mexicans.
Oh, because they're mostly white, though, you know, but they do have a lot of Indians up in the mountains and in South America.
So yeah, I don't have my best friend is from Mexico.
So can you speak some Spanish?
Come on, please tell him for you to sit there and call my friend a fucking rat
No, fuck you be the June be the jewels fuck you
You want the pants back? You want to continue blackmailing your ex-friend that you screwed over?
I don't give a fuck anymore. I'm done
You literally are shitting on Jamie. Who's my fucking friend? Not any more
Pitting people each other which is uncool. You're literally fucking crazy
You don't give a shit about me beta when I was in Cali
Not once did you ever let me come to your apartment and we're so-called besties?
I'll let you into my life with my mom
Fuck you beta. Hate you
And Rick, if you want to continue talking to Bita, you can lose me too.
And you know I'm a fuck controller, fuck mole.
Fuck, I'm sick of the drama.
Well, but she'll hate mine with all these people she mentions.
Oh, come on, call this out. Bita, maybe stop talking sexually on me
because you were really embarrassing when I was getting my hair done.
It was a really embarrassing call.
Yes
She even thinks you're the common denominator
Pitting people against each other. So fuck you beta and damn straight. I did tell gamble
We had a fallout you want to know why you threatened to call the police on me. That's why I
Prevent a lady to
Internet just wait a second
Bitches nuts. There's some videos of Barb
Coming at crypto. Oh beat I call the police on me, but you have my news weird, right?
Okay, go ahead do it call the cause I don't go fuck you go from calling the cubs to to literally saying happy birthday
Then you sit there and say oh I use you for money
You're gonna throw your gifts into my face
From the years before
Because I got Jamie that ring that ashtray didn't want her to ring a hundred dollar ring that they threw away
How about I give you your fucking pants back to that? I never fucking wore cuz I knew you would do something like this beta
You want to know why you lost all your fucking friends beta because you can't fucking keep a secret. That's why
That's not true.
So who's the rat?
Not Jamie, you're the rat, Bita.
So you don't know why I've been in so much shit
the past like, let's see, in the Abba shit?
It was all because of you, Bita.
You, Bita.
You live in some fantasy land.
And let me tell you, you and your friend,
you're in your 40s, acting all sexual, make that make sense.
Like I said, the oranges don't even exist.
And if you actually think, if you actually think
anyone can 5150 me, Bita, you're a fucking snake.
Because if I was at your place, no one would have 5150 me.
Because you know what? It's bullshit. That is a bullshit excuse. You know what's sad when you do watch this live?
Hey, you wouldn't even invite me to your front porch. Yeah, Gamble let me neither. Don't care if I show up on his front porch
Some friend you are really beta some friend
Yeah, you fucking snake-ass bitch. Whoa
You cause a lot of the problems on yourself Vita because this is what you do you do
I'm sick of you. So beta go take my nudes and shove them up your fucking asshole
You lying ass bitch
You're the biggest snake
And all you do is hurt people and then you wonder why I get pulled in drama is because you're the one that's messy as fuck
Not oh damn you beta
So guess what shove my middle finger put it up your ass because I'm done with you for life
And we agree when you care more about stupid podcast with Michael Doyle's than your own friends. That's the damn truth
You don't even ask anyone how they're doing
You lost all your fucking friends
Because of you beta because you try to play sides and you know what the ones that are loyal are the ones that aren't snitches
So go take your ass back to Ella and try to manipulate again because it's not
gonna work because you try to use people as weapons. You're using Karen as a weapon.
You use me as a weapon. You use other people as a weapon.
But you never admit when you're wrong beta and you let me take the fault every fucking
Yo, can you pause it real quick? And I'm gone. You sit there you talk to Karen and you know it
So don't put that on me
All right, so when do you guys think her and beta are gonna be friends again?
pretty soon because they just hate Bond and you know Crystal thinks she's gonna
take Bita's channel down and become famous on her own or whatever and Bita
gives in to her they fight and then they're in communication again so who
knows how long that's gonna last. So she literally apologized to her earlier this
week or last week. Yeah this is like three years old video.
Yeah, this is three years old, but they've been going back and forth for a long time though.
Oh my god, you could literally get any clip of theirs and just put it into the timeline right
now. Exactly. Because Abita recently did a live the other day and kept it up against Crystal.
Yeah. So it's back and forth with them though, but it's the same thing. And then they'll go
Oh, hang on, I'm putting that guy, you know, it's a tape model.
And Crystal thinks she's going to take, she always just wanted Sam Mann to be her simp.
I have that proof.
She was trying to take Sam away to help her with her channel because those people that
You know, they see through her and Q called Crystal out the other day because she always
tries to bring up, oh, my mom is sick or somebody's sick, I need to talk to you.
It's all bullshit because she's never there for her own family.
She did the same thing.
Her grandmother was sick and passing away, oh, she's dying, she's dying.
She was out in her car dancing to Britney Spears and on her way to get chicken wings and I messaged her privately
I said, what's going on crystal? You were crying about your grandmother and now there's a funeral going on today
And you're over there practically celebrating. Oh, I just can't do funerals. Well, then why did you cry about it all week long?
You know, you're you're celebrating and dancing to Britney Spears like nothing happened. She uses this when she gets caught doing shit
because she just reached out to somebody else. I was talking to
earlier to be the Oh, to be the two because she did it to
somebody else. It's going through personal thing.
Yeah, she's not. It's lies. That's what she does every time
when she gets caught doing shit. She has some tragedy going on
like her aunt. And I busted her out because her and her aunt
Amanda, Amanda, Amanda, and Erickson, I don't know a new person because I've never seen
that person before.
I'm not going to lie.
I thought that was supposed to be in X. No, no, no, hell, no, no, I don't look anything
like that, Arthur.
I'll even come up with you.
I just don't do it on YouTube.
Hey, baby cat.
Oh my God.
I think I think it's your voice.
Your voice makes it sound like you would look like the lady right there.
No, not at all. My voice is fine.
No, I'm saying it's a good voice.
I'm just saying, if it was those three ladies, I'd assume.
I got a good voice. Are you kidding me?
My voice made me money when I was working, though, too.
Really?
I am older, though, you know, but I'm not.
Did you work on the set-side line?
No, not that. No, I wouldn't do that.
I had a friend that did it for a while.
I want to show you guys something here, I want to get your ear.
I don't even look my age Arthur, I mean I still, you know, hit on by your guy.
Hidden layer of YouTube you rarely see on the home page.
It's an ecosystem of small channels, usually sitting between 1,000 and 5,000 subscribers
that operate almost entirely on internal conflict.
To keep youers engaged, these communities require a filming.
Without a shared enemy to target, lifestreams dry up, and the audience gets bored.
A creator known as Cult of Psyche became the designated target to fill that void.
Rival creators moved from petty insults to digital surveillance,
publishing his physical address and personal phone number for anyone to see.
From there, the attackers launched severe allegations to ruin his reputation,
explicitly accusing him of physically abusing his own cats.
This collective effort to dismantle a digital presence
marks the exact point where online conflict transforms into a targeted campaign.
The attackers maintain a steady barrage of public-facing hostility.
Channels like The Cate Show use their community tabs specifically to broadcast daily insults.
They flood these feeds with petty mockery,
regularly making posts dedicated solely to attacking his receding hairline.
When physical insults lose their sting, the attackers invent grotesque, absurd rumors.
They circulated claims that he was holding his cat's hostage and even spread a rumor that he consumed animal feces.
These fabricated stories serve a specific function.
By painting the target as entirely repulsive and unhinged, the attackers strip away his humanity,
ensuring no one in the broader community feels an ounce of empathy for him.
The harassment eventually shifts to covert economic sabotage, algorithmic starvation.
Instead of watching on YouTube, the attackers pirate the broadcast,
streaming his content inside closed third-party platforms like Discord.
This coordinated boycott starves the target's channel of vital metrics,
leaving zero algorithmic promotion.
To maximize the psychological cruelty,
the attackers closely monitor his empty ghost town chat from their external servers,
actively celebrating his lack of an audience.
On modern platforms, the ability to reroute an audience
is a primary tool of digital suppression.
Under the weight of relentless starvation and public attacks,
Psyche's behavior begins to visibly unravel.
His community posts become erratic.
He swings wildly between rescinding apologies to his attackers one day
Desperate to simulate a live audience in his empty streams,
he allegedly resorts to purchasing automated chatbots.
He even starts welcoming extreme outcasts onto his panel.
At one point, he invited a user who notoriously faked their own death,
seemingly just to have someone to talk to.
The bully's strategy of isolation creates a self-fulfilling prophecy.
By forcing the target into a corner,
they push him toward desperate behavior that only further alienates him from reality.
If you look at the livestream transcripts of the attackers after successfully isolating Psyche,
you find a surprising reality. The attackers openly admit their own community is becoming
pathetic, describing their daily drama as mind-numbing trash. Despite successfully isolating their
target, the attackers remain listless and bored. Hyper-insular digital communities operate on
a strict rule. Without the intervention of physical reality to ground them,
they will inevitably turn on each other to sustain the drama.
The Internet has given bullies a wider audience, but more importantly,
it has equipped them with algorithmic tools that make digital exile
and enforceable reality.
Hmm. Now, that makes sense.
Arthur dropped off.
I can't take the truth.
He can't handle the truth. He's afraid of Kate.
No, I like him. I didn't trust him before, though, you know, but he seems funny.
Thank you
Yeah, that was a man. You like the golden girls thing guy. I think yeah, it was a picture of a man
I mean
I don't know who Amanda is is that a new person? I've heard the name recently, but I don't know if she
Amanda actually I have myself fighting with her on rumble. I can show you it's not that I'm afraid of Kate
It's just I find it so obnoxious when you play AI videos when two people are having a conversation
Oh, it's like I am next to night. We're talking and then
Talk another video stop it. Oh my god
Because he's just about a resume Amanda because you guys who was Amanda I'm gonna show you there's a man fighting with me and saying
You sucky you're bad
Sike I found this video that Alex clapped. Uh, it was you know, she clapped it
you know I guess God works in mysterious ways I was going through everything on my phone and my
computer because I got it connected to my phone and I found this video that was clapped and I
have it I didn't know I still had it so that's thanks to this new laptop that my family got me
for my birthday but I can get it back up it was like what I thought all that was deleted because
I did a factory reset on my phone but somehow I brought it back up I don't know what I was doing
messing around and it did bring everything back up.
Awesome.
I gotta show you that video
because that's the guy's wife about Alex.
Well, this is like, yeah, I'm gonna see it.
Well, Tripp Kick hasn't posted in a long time,
but Amanda was a mod of mine and she's,
but now she's like, you know, she hates me now
because she-
I think Tripp Kick passed away.
He, oh my gosh, that's so sad.
He died here, you said?
I think he died in Minecraft.
Tripp kick? No wonder he's been gone. I like Tripp kick. The clip.
Yep. Well, rest in peace. I don't think he died. I don't know who it was, but I think it was somebody we know.
But here it is. I guess this is the Amanda. Let me see it, babe.
And so the only Amanda I know of is Zayas that the pebs her name is Amanda.
I thought they were talking about her when I mentioned putting my sharing
this staying silent isn't an option.
Amanda anymore though.
Amanda gonna hear limiting words go listen to be this stream tonight where she had a woman saying f a gg ot and
Niggi you're about a thousand times laughing all the way through with everybody on town laughing about it and also saying gay people should die
Listen to that
I thought you and Amanda were like like
like a lot. I like Amanda and Amanda went to Christine's and I heard like Christine talking all
this shit and Amanda was kind of like it's like they're not really you know and she would say
later she's like oh I like psyche and you know but I'm not expecting to defend him and stuff
she is my mod and stuff and just to be kind of in the enemy territory just like kind of like
Almost egging her on a little bit and so then she hid a bunch of people in my chat
And then she said that she was going to find my information too that pushed her over the edge
Did it come from her or did it come from here?
She said I'm money for 20s panel. Yes later in the day and she went on several panels complaining about me
I mean, I don't know anything about that.
I just figured that you and Amanda,
ever since I've known you, Amanda,
I've been on your panel.
I like Amanda, but until I looked at my block list
and she had blocked a bunch of people
and then she said she was gonna find my information
and I also told her,
Christina is straight out doxing my family
and she's like, well.
She just didn't seem to care and stuff.
She just didn't seem to care that much.
She did say, I didn't say,
tell me anything that defended me in that six hour stream.
And Amanda did say one sentence,
I like psyche and...
Yeah, I think he's a lost soul or something like that, but et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
I mean, that's all.
Then it's like, then it's like, then she goes back into the hate and says, I sent a, what's
the poem about?
And then she says about Danny stranger stuff.
And I lied about what Bita said, and I didn't know I would be a Bita said, Bita said, as
far as I can recollect, maybe I got the words perfectly right.
Okay, but let me just say, let me give you a second.
She said, Oh, and you're crying about that Danny changer guy and stuff.
I mean, I'm not perfect or none like that, but
Would you would you honestly agree that this has like changed you for the worst?
What is changed me the streaming or?
No, I'm how it's how it's getting compared to what you were when you first
I think I'm stronger. Hey, I'm okay. I have a couple songs to sing. I'm stronger than yesterday
Yeah, I want to put it on the record that you're absolutely by I have a clip on my community post
Now read it now anybody would like to go watch the short it's on my community
I can't play it now. I'm on my phone.
Can I play it? Can I play it?
I'm on my phone, dummy.
I can't play it.
Don't call me a dummy, man.
Don't call me a dummy on my show.
Okay, second of all.
Go to my community post.
I will right now.
Be clear.
People like why are you yelling at me Amanda? You know what? I'm tired of you lying on me. All you want is content
And I'm gonna play it now. I'm on my phone
Can I play it? Can I play it? I'm on my phone dummy
Don't call me a dummy on my show. Okay second of all
I will right now
People like why are you yelling at me Amanda? You know what? I am tired of you lying on me all you want is content
And i'm not going to be your fucking content
I am giving you notice to stop
Lady, stop slandering my name, how about that?
Do you understand me?
You are absolutely lying.
I never said I was getting your information.
I never said I worked for the government.
You are delusional.
You said you live on a military base.
You need help.
And you're going to get my information.
That is not what I said.
The clip is on my community.
What's your channel name?
If I can see, you can see my live.
Oh, hello.
What's your name?
Hello.
It's all my community posts.
What's your channel?
If I can go over to community posts.
Come on, tell me.
You don't know my channel? Um, I've been typing in your cat. What is it? Amanda Erickson? Yeah, it's Amanda Erickson
Clumsy, clumsy. I know you're his friend
I don't know if you can try to reason with him
This has been a downward spiral for about a week
I'm trying over it. You know, it's gonna be everybody year woman. Okay, but okay
You're ICK so in or you're ICS on all you do is click on my name in chat
And it will take you to my page. I have to go to my actual chat home. Just give me a moment and Amanda
You know, we can chill and like not. Oh, no, we're not friends anymore. I'm proving to you
You're absolutely delusional and you're listening to people also clumsy
I never hit anyone Kate and RG and that whole group told him that I was hiding people
He never checked the chat. They had him take my wrench
Okay, I made that decision. They didn't have me do anything. Okay, man
I absolutely did because I haven't clipped also. I made that decision. But who was hiding people then?
I have no idea. I didn't hide anybody if I hit someone I'd tell you I don't give a shit
There were as many people that are my friends that had no reason to be hidden
Do you know there are other people here who have a wrenches besides me?
I would have discussed it with you and stuff and you could have come up after RG
We could have-
But because RG and Kate told you you went with it because you're paranoid and delusional and you just believe anything people tell you
You're paranoid and delusional. That's why you're not wrenched, okay?
Don't care about your stupid wrench
Your your channel is not that important people have tried to help you and you shit on all of us
All of us what?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
You're the you're being a little cowlady. I'm actually not a locale
Cow in the cow gang, okay, no, they are thriving off of this
You know what? I find it very disgusting that you were calling Bronzeberg the n-word over and over
I have the clip
You disgusting human being. So I'm putting it on the record. It's on my short if anybody wants to go see and it proves
Psych is a liar. Let's find out right now. I'm gonna go right now. There's your chair. You are you're too drunk and high
I'm not drunk and high at all, lady. Okay, I'm gonna go. I've been watching you've been drinking all night quit lying about the fact
One two Buddha rangers
We're on something because you can't even comprehend you're on something
Do you have a picture of Ruth Gator Ginsburg with a crown on your page?
It's none of your business. Why do I have to answer to you because I'm asking you nicely. Okay, uh, because I
Where's the audio
You have a chat clip, you don't have an audio clip. Okay, so you don't know what you're talking about
Go to my shorts and play the video
I don't see. Okay shorts. Okay. There's the video. Okay
Psyche stop lying. Okay. Oh, let's play with you. Let's make a beat. It said about Danny stranger and I mean
Play the clip quit deflecting play the clip. I'm gonna play it right now Amanda. Do you want to see if I say it or yeah
I want to be here for it when you apologize. Okay, let's see and God you have to wait backstage because you're in trouble Goddy
I'll just I'll say that
Okay, you can come in a minute, but okay, Amanda. Let's go ahead and play it. Let's play your clip
Okay, let me get it up and I'm happy to play it and let's see what it here's a sweet beta
Good hearted beta said about my friend that literally about beta
This is about a cliff that you accused me of saying on money. I have pulled the clip. Please stop deflecting and play it
Not dyslexic. I'm playing it right now. Okay. You keep mentioning other people that
Please stop talking over it. Okay, this is your page, right? Correct. I guess so it's so small play the one on the left. Okay
He doesn't like us and because in the south that the fucking list I got my name on there Sam and me to Christine
Well, she got a couple of other people on there. Okay
I live at Little Rock Air Force Base. Okay, that's it
I just go ahead and get into the punch. Okay, I'm 50 years old. All right, I can talk about now 58
People who never stop asking are the ones who find answers
Questions are everything
Going so fast. Can I slow it down a little bit? It sounds like the gym monks are singing a song
Okay, I'll go down if you want to okay. It sounds too fast for me. Okay. I'll just I'll just play like it
It's because you're high and you can't you can't deal with it. You didn't be going slower
If you're big enough boy to come on down here, you just let me know
I'm saying what I'm saying is I'm gonna let this be known
I don't I'm gonna say this directly on the channel right now easy
It's funny how I try to have a conversation like conversation with you like a man
She doesn't like us and because I got my name on there, Sam, man,
Dita, Christine, um, well, she got exiled.
That was the end of the clip.
You're playing it again.
Okay.
That's an awesome song.
I just got my friend, Danny, on that clip.
Are you playing the long clip or what?
Excuse me.
That is my clip.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're drunk on the high.
Hey, the one on the left.
Everybody on the left.
You lied.
He literally lied on me and said that I said I was going to get his information and that
I worked for the government. I just provided a clip. That is not what I said. Okay, let's play it again.
No, this is okay. This is money for 20s panel. Okay. Well, I do. Okay. Well, what about the
Danny stranger? I don't give a shit about another clip.
Okay, you're out of here lady. You were accusing me of slaying by the Danny stranger clip on beta show not about money for 20 show
So you're out of here. Okay out
What is this shit? What is this bullshit? I said get a clip about Danny stranger and what beta said and now she's playing some clip
Or she's yelling about an Air Force base and stuff. I mean
clumsy
Who's that picture of?
Baby's mom. Who is that? My baby mama. Okay
That's your baby's mom. I thought you'd like big girls
No, you can't you can't tell who that is
No, I don't recognize that person. It's not his wife pride to the teeth. Who is that? Is that so Marie?
Yes. Oh shit
Clumsy stop it. I got you. I'll switch
Who's some rude that are teeth
Amanda, I didn't ask you, okay, okay, if I got whatever you said about the Air Force base wrong, okay, that's one thing I asked for you said you I was lying about beta and my friend Danny stranger who and I told you several times, where's the clip of beta talking about Danny, and then you have this other clip and stuff like that.
Yeah, yeah, what the fuck am I waiting for? Okay, so
Get rid of her get rid of her get rid of her
She's not gonna stop you guys are you serious or is he being silly? I don't want to be
I'm gonna say this one time and I need to go. I do have a life outside of YouTube
You told me to get a clip
You told me to get a clip from money 25 minutes ago please try to comprehend you accused me
Saying that I'm going to get your information and that I work for the government. That is not
You said you're on a military. That is what the clip proves. I did not say
Talking about Danny stranger
Over that's what you slandered me over a man. I call me a liar
You don't but you don't have that clip you said you pulled that clip you don't have clumsy. Um, he doesn't comprehend what I'm saying
Okay, you don't have that clip. I'm not interested in hearing anymore. It's like I know about whatever he said on money for 20s
I'm asking what you said what you said Bita has said, okay, Amanda
I'm not trying to be terribly rude or whatever, but it's like you're deflecting over the beat and Danny
This is what I was concerned about. Okay. I'm not really concerned about it. I know you're not gonna be
I'm hopefully, you know, looking for my information and stuff. Okay. Can you go find the beta talking about Danny stranger, please?
That's what I was asking about
not about
anything that I already have the transcripts for, okay?
I'm asking, we were accusing me of being a liar today
several times, accusing me of accusing Bita of lying and stuff
or something, whatever, okay?
Find that clip.
I don't care about that.
I know, ultimately, you're a good person.
I'm having serious, serious doubts about Bita, okay?
I'm lazy.
Yeah, I wanna go,
To rumble right now after you already said you found the clip and I want to go listen to six or seven hours of beta
Talking shit about me to find her talk shit about my friend when I'm asking you for a five second clip that your city already found
Okay, I'm a liar. Okay. That's why you're not a mod. Okay. I'm trying to be as calm as possible Amanda
But you are deflecting you are not
You are not telling the truth. Okay, you're trying to confuse me. You're trying to gaslight me or something you're on the HEPPER gang
Okay, I know it. I know it. Oh, it's not a real gang. Oh, it's not
Why do I see you dress up?
Come on in that Halloween picture with guns
Why is that Amanda?
What come here?
Come here. Leave that. No, no, no. There's no answer clumsy
Don't mess with the bully. I don't even know what's really going on on that
Do you haven't heard of the head for game? Yeah, no, no like what she's talking about
The other night
Oh, oh, he's crying about his dumb friend, Danny Danger.
Oh, and, and, you know, he's like trying to get cloud
off of his death.
Okay.
Cause I made a memorial video of my friend
that got shot in the chest three times three weeks ago.
And then she's like, oh, psyche's a liar about that.
Cause I listened to beat this clip
and she's not making fun of Danny stranger.
And I was like, that's the clip I wanted.
Now she's
Slaying a clip I already heard about her
I heard that clip I heard that one
I didn't need that clip Amanda. I needed the Danny stranger clip, which is so that's what I asked you about. Okay. It's okay. You guys are okay
Did you see what I made today
I didn't see it. No, I didn't make your promise. I'll make yours. You're thank you, but I mean
Yeah, your banner. I'll make that but look what I made
Hope you're proud of me
Join the cult of Christine punch break initiation
Bridge of emotional support harness included is that supposed to be Christine?
Yeah, really young. What you think? Yeah, I mean, I mean, I'm not like gonna be mean and stuff like that
I'm literally said I'm beat is go jump off a bridge psych and I mean it jump off a bridge and die
Okay, look at the alligators. They look kind of small. She said there's alligators
She told me there's alligators, but she said it was rich up being with the harness and stuff
So she has the harness so she hates you that much. She told you kill yourself on yes and be the
Beta said stop saying that Christine cuz that's like probably the fifth or sixth time she said it in the past few days
Wow. Wow. There we go.
No, don't do that. You're going to get the bully to come at him.
Come on, calm down. Come on, Gwyneth.
Okay, I have, I'm going to have this, I'm going to have this one analyzed.
I think this is when Vita...
Calm down, it's okay.
I think this is when they did the spider ritual.
I'm going to have this episode analyzed. Hold on a second. I need to transcribe.
Okay, so I next oh shit what I have I have some things I've been exciting game to play with you
If you'd like to play a game this is I have a game of my game show set up
Okay, okay
I mean I gotta take this call. It's it's my best friend. Hold on. Hold on. If I drop off. I'll come back up. Okay here
Okay, but guys look I have
Love it
Now presenting on Coltkodex.me and the Coltoseggie and Peggy's Nightmares and all the good stuff.
Here we go. Presenting. Hold on. I need to search for something else real quick.
I got this. Here we go. Are you ready to go to this, guys? I hope you'll like this.
You guys, how are it, sir and fans? Check this out. Keep it going.
Yeah, hi, is this the adult store?
Uh-huh.
What can I assist you with?
Well, me and my buddies were having a bachelor party,
and I was wondering what kind of sexy games,
board games you have?
Uh, all different kinds on you.
You would just have to come in and look at them.
Well, can you let me know if you have hungry, hungry dildos
where you stuff one of your buddies' asses with meatloaf
and then whoever digs it out with a dildo first wins?
Honey, I have like 20 or 30 games.
Well, can you just let me know real quick if you have cockopoly,
where the buddy who can put the most game pieces in their pee-hole wands?
Honey, we don't have any of the ones like that.
Do you have battleship where you shape your turds into the shape of a ship
and then you throw it at all your buddies?
I am not going to sit here on the phone for half an hour
and explain to you what we do and do not have.
I don't have time.
Well...
i was just curious do you have pin the pecker inside the donkey's asshole
where which everybody can fight off the other one to get to bang a blow up donkey first wins
no honey because something with a donkey is illegal it's bestiality no it's not a real donkey
it's a blow up it doesn't matter oh do you have connect for skin where two uncircumcised guys
connect their four skins together and then another buddy tries to separate them with his tongue.
We don't have the type of games like that. Oh, you don't. We have fun, sensual party games,
not raunchy ones. Do you have splatter goreys where one buddy with diarrhea splatter shits on the
This is getting to the point that this is a little ridiculous keeping me on the phone for half an hour talking about things that you shove in someone's anus
It's not very cute. Well, I just want if you would like to know what we have in our store
Come on in what do you have poop shoots and ladders?
No, you climb a ladder and then you try to shit in your buddy's mouth below and whoever shits it
first wins
Hello
Alright, welcome back to SwampShop. Let's go back to our phones. Good morning. Welcome to SwampShop.
Good morning. How are you today? I'm doing well. How about yourself? I'm doing fantastic.
Can you stay warm though? I'm trying. There you go. I have diabetes,
so I really have to keep my feet wrapped. Oh, definitely. Yeah.
Well, anyway, I'm selling a program here. I got this from my grandchild, Rusty,
and it's a great program for kids. You type in a word and it gives you the proper pronunciation
Yeah, have you ever heard of such a thing?
Uh, no.
It's called Words to Sounds.
I'll give you an example like Swap Shop.
Watch this.
I'll put in Swap Shop.
Swap Shop.
You hear that?
Yeah.
That's pretty good, huh?
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
It's great for, you know, especially children who are blondos and whatnot.
I'll do another one for you.
I'll put in, uh, let's see.
I'll put in Nickel.
Watch this.
Nigger.
Oh, sorry about that.
No, that's not the right one.
Let me try bike.
It's not working for you hold on
That's it. Oh geez hold on one second. All right
Put on my chest. All right, we can't do that. All right. You're gonna get me in trouble there. Sorry about that and
Okay, it could be a great program, but not with that kind of language, especially on
the air.
Good morning.
Welcome to Swap Shop.
Good morning, Wildman.
Hey there, Mikey.
How are you doing, sir?
You know, that's pretty sad that got none of the Swap Shop like that, saying that kind
of stuff.
I like to let them in for decent, respectable people, you know, that are trying to be nice
to everybody and help one another, and then they got to get on there and act like an idiot.
Yeah, well, that won't happen again.
I like to catch him at Walmart parking lots all the time.
All right, thank you.
Okay, wow, man.
You have a good day.
Stay warm.
You too.
Okay, bye-bye.
Good morning.
Welcome to Swap Shop.
Hi, how are you today?
I'm doing well, how are you?
I'm good.
I just wanted to apologize to you about that caller
that was with bad language.
That was legitimately an accident.
That was my husband.
He shot off some of his fingers squirrel hunting
and he can't type the best.
That is a legitimate machine that we are selling.
Oh, thanks.
And I'd like to put it up there.
OK, and your number?
I want to just let you know that it doesn't just do words, it does full phrases so that
kids can use it in school. Like I'll type in, I'll type in, my husband Fred loves when I bake him
a dinner cake and it'll say the full sentence. My husband Fred loves when I blow him. All right,
21 minutes after 9 o'clock, I apologize again.
That was my best friend.
There's something going on.
So I got a rush over there right now.
Her mom and her just called me.
I'll be back in a little bit.
I'll probably be back within an hour.
So I don't know what's going on.
Something's happening.
Brandon's going to be back stage.
Brandon's on it.
I accidentally just brought him up.
He's be printing to be you right now.
Why I mean he needs to chill out, you know one thing about him and he's not too faced
I thought he was gonna be too facing all about these people because I've had enough
Well, so I don't know if he chills out and didn't have him up
I mean, you know, he says I and X, but he has your picture up the pic in the old picture. Yeah. And you've seen me Brandon. He's seen me. Okay. And remember, I lived at 7912 Charter Trail at the Academy of States there in Albuquerque. Go take a picture of that home. Okay. With a pool and everything.
Yeah, I don't know. He just goes nuts and you know, I don't know. You know, because I thought he was actually cool in the beginning.
Then he just goes totally nuts and playing old recordings or whatever and I don't know
But I actually thought he was real too and he's not
Take care of take care of your friend. Yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna go over there right now better hurry
So yeah, I'll talk to you later, but he just needs to chill out and you know, maybe oh
Yeah, he's okay. I did a screenshot of him. I can go ahead and do lots of him too. She called you a meth head yesterday
I never called you a meth head
Where's the proof Brandon? Why do you keep lying? You know, but I appreciate you for not being so two-faced
Yeah, you know, so
Yeah, I mean if he chills out man because you know that a lot of the stuff that was said about him is wrong
You know and then I started going along because he pissed me off
Brandon is not a pedo
Okay, you know and I don't know
Huh, you know feebo file. No, he's not that either. No, that's somebody else. It's evil file and he knows who he is
Okay, you know and and I remind him every time I see him
Well, I am next. I'm so sorry, but I always thought you and what was the other lady Amanda? Mm-hmm
I thought you guys were the same person you said that one time before and that's what people said
No, I mean she was new at that time. I remember her now. I didn't know she was still around
My goodness you guys sound the same. Oh
No, we do not yes psyche. Do you think they sound the same?
They have a similar accent a little bit.
They have a very similar accent, right?
Oh my God, an accent.
Yeah, damn.
That's like saying that Brandon is clumsy.
Whoa!
And clumsy is the piece.
He's a, uh, man.
Well, hold on. You don't get along with clumsy?
No, man. He's a piece of shit. He's an asshole and he got caught lying with his stupid fake DMs that he had
saying it was from Bita, or I don't know, this bullshit. I know, I can't stand, Clumsy, you're a piece of shit.
Whoa!
That's, I can't stand him.
That's my buddy.
Yeah, no he's a piece of shit. Oh damn. He's actually gonna be doing a
What is this a lasagna stream later today? Really eating again? Yeah, well cooking cooking. Yeah
Yeah, that's all he does him and his wife eat a lot. Oh
Come on
Yeah, I mean you've seen the real picture shit using my old one should I'll even came up for Brandon
Psyche you call you yeah, Brandon doesn't know we came up. Yeah
And then am I big no
You you said I'm a size three or four I said I wear a size seven now
But if he'd be chill out because he's a smart guy and he had good things to say and he's funny
And it just went to hell and I don't know. I just
And then crystal back and forth back and forth and I don't know
He's just we're about to play around to the panel for his game show. No, no, it's okay. We're talking. We're talking actually
It's okay. Yeah
No, no, no, no, no, we're good. No, it's okay. Anyways, um
so
Okay, okay. Well, it talks about Brandon because he's really smart and he has a little go out of good things to say and I noticed he's not too faced.
Oh God Karen is awful.
So much for her marriage is an asshole. Yeah, to face. And he's an ass.
Kisser. He's a stamp. He's a beat a stamp. Everybody knows of him.
I think he used to be. I think you woke up.
He's up all night with her kissing her ass and ball this shit.
He doesn't know me, you know?
Yes. In the past, I've done some shit.
I was also a cokehead and doing all this shit for some guy.
And so that's what Bita brings up.
And I've already talked about her past
and the rest of it is going to come out
because her ex-friends are ready to talk.
And now Eldo can communicate with them
so they go live with him.
They're not going to go on with Bita separately
to be yelled at and talked over.
They want to go on live with somebody to speak on Bita.
He's saying you have no self-awareness at all.
Oh, yes, I do. He doesn't even know me. He doesn't. That's why he's on panel all night
long with his bald self. It's like, get a life. Come on, maybe not married. I mean, he's
he's sad. Everybody, you know, they, they, I mean, the same could be asked about you.
Yeah, I know. And then he doesn't know me and I don't know him. Maybe he is a better
person. I don't know. I just see an asshole all in the middle of drama.
I mean, we're in the middle of drama right now.
I mean, you guys are different, but he's a gossiper,
like women can be.
I don't see you doing that.
Oh, no, I definitely am, trust me.
Well, not about good things that you know,
but to him, just he's a simp, you know,
and I don't respect them.
Well, the other day he cursed her out,
he went off at her, so I don't think he's a simp.
He simps for her and believes everything she says
when the truth is out there
and she's gonna be exposed by her ex-friends.
just like Eldor is exposing her.
I have those videos, I have them on private,
the video about beta doxing people to them.
I have that.
If you wanna see that, I'll send you the link.
It's unlisted, but I'm gonna put it on Rumble.
I mean, she doxed me a lot of it.
What's your Rumble's channel's name?
I gotta look at it. I think I have it under Inexcessive X. I've had it for a while, so I gotta look because I'm gonna go ahead and start uploading there.
I'd only use it sometimes to watch stuff on Rumble, so I don't know if it's under Inexcessive X. I think it is under that name.
But I'll give it to you.
You know, as soon as I log on, right now, my best friend called and so I got to go over there for a little bit, but I'll be back, Arthur.
We'll be here.
And yeah, I'll be back in psyche also has my G on there that you can add me on.
We are waiting the salmon flight probably over here.
I know. Yeah, get a Vita flag for one that is whatever his name is.
One that is.
One that is whatever his name is, a thing or whatever.
He calls himself thing or, you know, thing, miss thing.
So, okay, well, I better, she just texted.
I better run over there.
Thank you.
Okay.
We'll talk later.
I'll be back later.
Saki, I'll be back in an hour.
Thank you.
Okay.
Bye guys.
All right.
Rain, uh, rain left.
Wow.
Rain falling on my finger.
Well, I guess now that it's you and me.
Yeah.
Like the old times, I gotta say this.
Have a good day.
I gotta say this for the old times sake.
Ladies and gentlemen, anything and everything that psyche has done
and said, especially with Brandon Q, I do not agree with.
Never will I agree with.
I would talk more, but my mouth is full right now.
What the fuck?
What are you doing?
Giving you a blue job.
Whoa, chill.
We don't agree with what he has done and said
and his companionship with Brendan Q.
We stand against that and...
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
What the hell?
Oh my god, Arthur, that was so good.
Thank you for your big load.
Wait, Karen was talking shit about you yesterday, Psych?
No.
That's the thing that is, is sad just now.
It was not as a misunderstanding.
Oh my, like I said, one day in this community...
is, like, a whole year.
Wait, well, you know, I was already filled by somebody,
but one day for me, I aged, like, a month every day.
I look like I'm 100 years old now.
I'm bald, I'm a monster.
So I'm not on camera anymore.
I've used that old picture of myself.
And I've got fantasies.
Maybe the thing that is can do a panel?
Maybe you can.
If you can get off the beach,
probably on the beach with a drink and a process, you.
I'm about to take a nap.
Hello? Yeah? Oh, he said he's coming up. He's gonna come up. Hold on, I'm gonna put the link up. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to think. I was just joking about the process, you.
I know he doesn't do that kind of thing. He's about to go for lunch. Now he's, oh, now I said no. Now I said no.
Oh, wow, never mind. It's mine. Now he's about to go to lunch, so I made that joke. I'm so sorry.
Well, I'm gonna put that picture up so we can have this spirited thing that is in the chat anyway.
This is what he looks like, guys.
Hold on, hold on. That's fine.
Well, that's supposed to be K.K.
No.
Not to be confused with him.
With different people.
And look, there's Arthur and the bikini.
Did you see the...
What is this?
Oh, my goodness, I forgot.
Oh!
Did you see the Photoshop photos of...
What's the Korean girl's name? Crystal?
That's a man had played yesterday.
Oh, the Photoshop. I didn't know it was Photoshop.
What would they look like? I thought it was...
Oh, my God.
They put her...
They put her face on, you know, the Thomas and Friends train?
Oh, the train? Oh, she doesn't have a train.
Because you got a big forehead?
Yeah, I can do that picture at home.
It's like, let me see if I can do this.
Put her on a yellow train, though.
Okay, hold on.
I need to get her face on.
Hold on. Let's see if anybody can do it.
They got a picture home. Oh, we have a guest. Let's welcome to the show
Hello, yes, baby. Let's come on. So you can't let you know you can't let these people woods like you know
You can't let these people
You gotta hit them hit them where it hurts, you know
I know I'm going shit. I'm going shit, but so yeah
Underdogs right now, you know, we don't underdogs, you know, we don't we ain't our kissing ass
You know like like like beta and Sam and trying to fucking play moral police and think they're better than everybody
You know, we don't die. I don't die. I don't go low. I don't talk this shit
I don't talk that shit, you know Arthur does it, you know, I do it site. He does it, you know, everybody does it
You know
You get what I'm saying like
Okay, yeah, I know we have to say to Arthur today. I think he left
Yeah, he left
Arthur making it does his deliveries right now. It'd be back
What do you mean? I'm right here
Yeah, did you hear two sides that his wife left them only been married like took three months
Your wife left you, Arthur?
You want to come live with me?
No comment.
You can come live with me in bed.
Yes, you found them with a gay man in bed.
What?
Was it with Zaya?
Oh, you said that.
I didn't say that.
You
For the record Zea if you listen if you're hearing this clip he
Didn't bring you up. He said the I don't think they're worried about you
This will be honest with you. I don't I don't think he worried about you, but you know
He's busy dealing with pubs, you know.
I don't know. Say, do you want to bend the knee and say sorry before he gets pushed off?
I'll get on my knees and suck.
Oh, my God!
Wait, didn't she say you would chew to get back at his discord, Arthur?
No, no, no, that's not true.
Oh, it's, you know.
All right, you know.
It's about to get Zay in here, instead of Gay Zay.
He's getting those fucking emails about streaming or 40% off screen. Yeah, yeah, I have I have the image are you guys ready?
Presentation to do I'm ready for the image. No wait, is it gay?
No, it's crystal. Well, yeah, it has to do with the train
And my butt, now I'm just gonna, hold on,
that's what I have to do with this one.
Here we go, are you guys ready?
This is the presentation.
Ever like Thomas the train?
This is the crystal engine.
We don't see anything, man.
Come on, bud.
Ha ha ha ha.
Come on, you try to say your head shape like top of the train. Come on. You want so you must you must want war with Chris
Chris come on. Why are you doing this?
That's her real picture. That's a bad at it too, man. I ain't even good at it
That's a bad at it too. You know having her on ET the ET one was pretty good
You know the the one on the foot on the poo poo platter was funny
They had one where she looked like the brother of her alien or whatever, that was pretty good.
They got good ones.
They do got good ones.
Yeah, I'm fixing it because that was too like photo realistic. That's I mean I think I wanted her to look
You know, but my picturing was like she was actually one of like the real Tom's the train gang
Like she was actually like they had her face, but it was more like you know has that like dinner like oh here
I think I did it. I think I did it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Here's what it would look like
Okay. Okay. Hold on. I got to say that a special way.
Yo, while you do that's like, why happened when you and Jamie's Cowboys?
She was your top mob, right? Why did you turn on her? Why?
I mean, I mean, she's she's busy with with some stuff right now.
But she was watching.
Oh, okay.
I mean,
you're real quick, you're just ready. It's ready.
This is what she really looks like.
The train.
It's getting image.
Thomas was a pillar
Newborn child. Yeah, do you like that one? That was good under dog. Oh, you so they said when you want to do it under dog
Okay. Oh, hold on. No, no, I found it. No. No, sorry. That was the wrong one. I have the right one
Okay, it does like it was like here. This is a cartoon of
Yeah, that was identical man. I was so identical. Yeah, I know this one's better
This is more of like the in between that I was looking for so this is what she looks like as
Thomas the train if she was Thomas the train Crystal Anne as Thomas the train. Is that better?
Yeah, hold on. No, that doesn't look any better. Don't you have AI? I mean, it's there.
Yeah, like you can ask AI, hey AI, put this face.
I'm happy to look at problems like slandering people, so it's saying, oh, you can't do it.
I have to like put a specific way.
So I'm going to try, I'm going to try and get them.
So we should put her face on an underdog.
Okay.
No, you just ask AI, hey AI, make her look like a Thomas and friends train character.
And it's saying it's offensive to trains.
No, you just don't know how to type it in.
You're not as good as I thought you were with the AI.
Where's your AI?
I want to see your crystal lambs right in 10 seconds.
Really?
I don't even have a photo of her, though.
Well, I mean, see, you can't even do that.
I mean, I got a photo of her.
I mean, I'm doing all the kind of work.
Like, you can just, you know, copy what I have.
See, she's on the screen.
Is she on the train?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you just copy this one.
Roy.
All right, now you can just have a photo.
Just do a screenshot of that.
No, I don't want my her photo on my my phone, you know
Well, you think about my picture. You don't see my picture. What do you think man? It ain't my picture. I stole it
Is that oh my god, who do you think? Who do you think it is Arthur? Who do you think it is like?
You know, a little heavy set, you know, a little fatter than usual, but
Still the you know faces there. What y'all think Chad? Who do you think my image is man?
that Vita
Full screaming man, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see man, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat see, let the chat
Well, I came I came at that woman in those movies. I put you know Crystal Anne's face and I came at that
Who's that heavy-set comedian?
You know that lady that she's on like that, you know that always were Jason Bateman and she's identity theft and she's like real funny
She goes, oh, hi. She's not bad looking. She's not bad looking, you know, right there
That's a comedian, right?
Crystal Anne's yeah
Go ahead Arthur do the beat imitation and then yeah, okay, there we go
Yeah, I think Arthur's good
You may who gave you this one did you make this one with AI or somebody gave you that from the real pictures
Yeah, those are the real pictures, and I made the and I made the AI I slightly
Made them a little bit better be just so you can't use your shit numbers
He said all the paper that can't use my stuff is psyche
And now so I had a couple more people as she goes
Whoever uses your shirt, baby
Street like they kill somebody by force feeding her and I think that's like the
picture it makes okay, hold on
I don't know pretty good. Oh
Shit, okay
Found on rumble actually found that we're not really Arthur are you here?
He's gone
So what do you want to do Elvin?
Nothing honestly, you know, I thought I'd catch you I had something to do I came back and you know Karen
Oh, there is you're doing parents supposed to give me that information on you know, you know, you know, you know, Jamie and
Locker on IG she said
I'll think about it
Yeah, I'm dealing with crystal right now. I can't deal with multiple people, you know, I can't can't can't multi-task
I can't have two of them, you know, I can deal with one at a time
Three some and you're a three some of the other man and I can only deal with one at a time right now
To be honest with you, but what you do that anything else to cover are you done playing clip? So what are you doing?
Despite original if you want to hear some of the spider ritual show
I mean it was you know what I think you should do because people make it fun to you, right?
You know you try to you know you try to rebrand and shit, you know
But one thing, you know, you gotta leave these weirdos alone, like Brandon Q, you know, you
gotta leave them alone.
But honestly, maybe get donations from some of your top mods, you know, and try to get
a haircut, you know, get a beard trim, a haircut, and come back, you know, come back a new guy,
you know, clean your fingernails up, you know.
Hello.
Honestly, you know what you should do?
Get a kid, get a little kiddie.
Get a kitten, you know, try to rebrand.
Try to have people like you, you know what I mean?
Because right now, people are not fucking with you.
So, like, you don't need to rebrand.
Get a kitten, you know?
Don't get a kitten or something, you know what I mean?
Can you move in with me?
You know just trying to
Like like
Trying to make fun of my voice with fucking Arthur Arthur is already like, you know, you think he does a good impression
I don't know. I think he's just retarded, but we got
Like sweet pea this guy like it's been nocturnal like he's some kind of a like I don't know
Come he's like some kind of a nocturnal fucking like being was saved up all night
and sleep all day probably, okay? Drinking white fucking alcohol, smoking weed and he's
going to judge me. Meanwhile, I'm not married and I don't have any kids, but he does. Figure
that one out. Figure that one out. Why a grown-up man needs to be fucking obsessing about me.
How many of them? How many are there? Hi Stargazer.
Christine, would you like the link, please?
Good morning, Sunshine.
Christine, come up.
I know I will, then be still commanding you.
Good morning, ladies.
Hi, Stargazer, how are you?
Hi, Sweet Pea.
How are you?
I'm going to look up for the spider.
Hi, Stargazer.
It is early in the morning.
I was like, oh shit, was she up all night?
And then I'm like, oh no, a spider's done got her attention.
Come on.
I lost my friend to teeth, Bronx birds.
This is how I talk now.
That's it.
Do we have all good at that?
Okay, Clumsy shut the fuck up. I sleep fucking like pretty early every fucking night just cuz I did a couple of all nighter
I don't do it all the time
I'm single. I'm not married. Why don't you go cuddle and spoon with your wife and spend time with her you weird
Don't get a graveyard
shift
We'll get a job so you can fix those two front teeth you look hideous
When I'm not actually slept in bed with your wife. That's my question ladies
Would you step out of the house with two fucking front-missing teeth?
No, no, would you come up on fucking YouTube with two front-missing teeth?
Don't get your shit fucking fix instead of seeing up all night
It's showing all the weed you bought and drinking alcohol and talking about females and putting them down
They want to they want to talk about
Drunks, okay. They want to talk about drugs. We're gonna talk about drunks. Okay. Oh god
Oh, yeah, we're gonna talk about drunks. Let's talk about it. Yeah, we need to talk about drunks because
um, who here?
Not on panel
But who goes into another chat and calls the people that are up all fucking night?
drinking
Smoking pot and god only knows what other kind of drugs
Okay, but they want to call this woman
Now I'll call her
I mean bring him up. Let's give him the smoke. Well, he's gonna let me finish first. Yeah
And you listen until Christina's finished, okay? Yeah
So, so you want to hear, you want me to give you a list of the drunks, um, probably the top one on the list, but I've been trying to do better.
No, no, no.
You are not breathing every fucking day.
Yes, she was all night.
Yes, she was.
Look, look, it's a fucking blazer.
While you're a fucking blazer.
You are not.
You are not a fucking blazer, Sipy.
I'm not a fucking blazer.
I don't know.
She laughing at her.
I'm not going from McDonald's.
I'm not bashing fucking like people all night long
based on their looks, their age.
And I'm not going and I'm not a man going out woman.
I don't know.
Don't know sorry
You don't want to call psychodrunk come on
I'm choosing violence again today
I heard you were really rude to fucking you were really rude to a lot of people. What the fuck is wrong with you?
Well, you know, I
Have you ever asked clumsy why he stays up all night and he doesn't get to work to fix this fucking front tooth
Sam, I'm missing this from T2, Chad, come on now.
A lot of shit, but I did, when I did come in, it was like 30 minutes ago, when I was like alerted,
it happened to be you up there with fucking clumsy, a dumb fuck bitch who got fucking
claimed he got broomed up the ass, right? Not anybody else, missing tooth, saying I'm a fucking drunk
Uh, look at his panels. He's drinking.
Look at my weed, man.
Uh, okay, so she could just make false accusations?
It was not false.
Everybody else does.
It was also other names.
Name the people. Name the people.
You said people.
It's me.
Who are the people?
Hi, brother.
Morning.
Are you been outside?
Come on.
Sorry.
Are you been outside?
I'm out of here.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Morning.
Are you there?
Yeah, he is
Wait, hold on
Couldn't go against a man
Nice a man comes up these little weasels run
Thank you
Where did Arthur go?
He saw a man and he flew away. He can only go out women or gay man. He can be like
I did was say hello, I like Arthur kind of sort of sometimes
He does try to do this elbow thing. He just sucks at it like he wants
Arthur watch so
He said he's out of here. Yeah, what a baby. Yeah
Big batter G's here
Is here a man is here
Yeah, I can get it like you're sitting there saying this like a don't be hypocritical. Oh
Be that is so drunk be that wine. I never hurt anybody even you put all the women together
and combine them they do not equally fucking wine as much as psyche that one dude and guy oh
i know my viewers are lower oh i didn't ask you a question oh they stroke me oh everybody
hates me okay breathe shut the fuck up no breathe like our title and ask you a question we're never
on panel together but uh good would you ever talk to your like are you ever gonna pause it like
Come on so you gotta talk so you gotta give a little commentary site
You know she tried to do a list of the drunks, you know Christine old-ass, but she didn't want to add beta into that list
Like she just fucked up the whole thing, you know
Right, she should never brought up the drunk list the top ten top ten drunks when when beta at least top five
You must ago and be there's
This is a nine o'clock in the morning stream, but like you can tell they're all this is when they do the spider ritual on me and stuff
And they name the spider here at all but my thing
But but how can you be top?
How can you be top ten drunk if you can't afford to buy beer like beta every day? You know I'm saying
I must have my seal it, I must seal it from the store, okay?
Yeah, I don't get the context, you know, it's like,
Bita isn't a motherly figure, or, well, yeah, no, I would not, no, I wouldn't.
And listen, me and Blackboard do have our shit, but he still doesn't talk up stuff about me.
I like Bita, that's why I wouldn't, but I do say some horrible things to people.
so I might not be the best person to ask you for the interview.
You're being honest though, R.G. that worries me about asking you because I knew you would be honest.
And that's what most men will not do, and I appreciate you for that. You're a real man.
Who the hell is that? Yeah, I say horrible things, I don't believe it.
Is that a, you know what? We all do it sometimes.
You know what? At least you own a black card key. You don't go live the next day and act like Mr. Innocent and say
Everybody said I should go do this to myself. They're trying to do it
There was a live nine hours ago
He's doing the exact same fucking thing and he was doing the exact same fucking thing this morning
And he's trying to to put a narrative out there that when he chooses
to do something harmful to himself.
It's everybody else's fault.
Yeah, I would say he's the one with the weapon in his hand,
not us.
He seems to need a crazy woman in his life, though,
whether it be Emma or Alex or a very strong female.
How to drain lymph fluid like a true American.
This simple trick is transforming lives.
Sounds crazy.
But I couldn't skip another ad. So yeah, I'll come back with when you're not
What's like doing I think psych fella sleep man, I don't know
What are you doing?
What's walking the cat
Arthur up here Arthur don't fall asleep
Arthur are you there here?
Yeah, I was just trying to show you something. I was trying to show you a show. I'm sorry. I just did that was really cool
No, that was a good play in reference to Christine trying to name the top 10 drunks of you know, I guess YouTube or a panel versus some shit, but, you know what I mean?
We have either, I think we have I and X only.
I need bring bring Jamie up I and X bring Jamie up.
Good Jamie and Nancy being Nancy being Nancy being
Oh my god, quiet down boy cat. Jesus.
I just got back.
Oh, Jamie just had a wisdom teeth taken yesterday.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. You told me about that.
Crash down when I called her and she was like completely out of it.
Okay, so is it true that Jamie being using a lot of alts to harass Crystal Ann?
I mean Crystal Ann? No, no, Crystal makes that up. No, Jamie and Nancy don't make alts.
They're hardly on YouTube. Sometimes now they watch Beta because they were friends before,
but they don't go there with alts. You can even ask, hey, who talks to them? Even Shannon, she was
Nancy and even said she's beautiful, you know, Nancy is just private person. She's married
She does real life and she works
Some I don't know what she does some kind of vet type of thing because she was doing a live of a surgery
they were doing on some animal and
Even brick was on there watching asking her what's that surgery on or whatever, but no they don't make alts crystal lies
Because she makes alts
Okay, I can believe it. I can believe it and when you talk to them, you'll hear their story
You like them both, but that's why I said on IG because they'll do you know, you can communicate on IG, but they don't do this
Making accounts on YouTube
At all they use their own and Crystal used Jamie recently and made her mod to upset beta
And Jamie realized hey, she's just using me because of beta and so she ended up blocking our crystal for good
That's why Jamie's in her mouth now. She
Not show her complete communication with Nancy. She cut off her part
I got the rest of it and I posted it because she was saying oh, I want Jamie's body
Remember on that video that psyche played how she was talking about how she's sent her wedding ring or something
And that's I'm glad I need that clip though because she's denying that but yeah, she did buy them some cheap wedding rings her and Abba and
Then to Nancy recently because then Jamie looks great. She's she's real thin. She looks like a model and
She's lying and saying making fat pictures of her and Jamie will be FaceTime. She used to be on panels
Okay
Now now now is K still talking to Jamie and Nancy?
Who who is Kate the turtle still talking to Jamie and Nancy not not lately
They were gonna go up on panel with her. So they haven't but they talked to her
I don't know if it's in DMs or how but that's why Kate likes them
And okay, God, I'm beautiful. They are beautiful. You know Nancy's happily married
And Jamie is still single and she's doing great.
She owns her own hair salon business
and she's making a lot, a lot of money.
She's a hard worker.
Okay.
Now you and Barry still be talking behind the scenes
and things.
No, not anymore because it was just too much to be asked.
And I just, you know, don't talk to them anymore.
So no.
I mean, was he trying to get pictures from you too?
I mean, that's his thing, you know,
he tried to get pictures.
No, no, no, no, no, not at all.
We just coughed.
Yeah, no, he never tried to get anything from me.
We talked about weed and stuff,
and I'd shown him the weed I was getting,
this shroom joints that I got,
and he told me about the cones, you know,
and I started getting the cones
and I would send him pictures of that,
but no, we didn't exchange personal pictures or anything.
Just weed pictures basically yeah, because we both smoke weed
Yeah, he actually was cool, but then you know, I just got tired with the drama and all this shit
So I don't remember what happened now. I just ended up blocking a lot of people
You know so
Yeah, are you cool? Are you cool with him though? Or no, we still like
Been a while in a couple years
Yeah, and he didn't really do anything. I'm just fed up with the drama and me mentioned as you know, just I was done
talking to my enemies and
So I was done
I really don't play that game.
You know, all I do is like everybody tells me,
I just show receipts, even Alex was saying that.
And one of my worst enemies that we used to go at it
in real life, and you know what he said recently,
and I've hated him.
And he said something that was really nice
cause everybody was saying, y'all are getting along now.
Y'all had this war going on.
And he said, one thing about Karen,
he said that I found is she always tells the truth
cause she'll even bust herself.
when she's involved in something so and he said that's what I respect her for and it was like wow
that was nice coming from my big time enemy oh they say you were real they say you were real
yeah I was shocked that I was shocked he said that because you know we still go at it or we did
go at it before and it was nice I was surprised he even said that and he's and I said wow I said
You know, and we used to go at it though. Although he was like we were enemies
I'm alive and then him saying that at the end in front of everybody and they were shocked
It's like wow y'all are cool now and and he said yeah
And he said that's what I respect about you Karen
He said that in front of these people and it's like I was shocked. It was like wow
You know, so yeah, I always show proof and everybody knows that
But I come with receipts and sometimes it gets me in trouble though too. Maybe that's going a little too far
But I'll show the truth. It's like no you're lying about this because this is what I'm showing proof
This is what you said and it came from you, you know, and I like that you do that too, although
I think the question is are you going to go back to Alex, I mean, you know, I know I'm done, we had, we, she called me twice the other day, she even texted me to give her a call, because you know she was saying she was going to pull up on me and do this and I said go ahead because I got your apartment number and I said it.
And then she said, and I said, I'm pulling up now because she was saying on the live that she was pulling up and she was going to bring a body cam or and then she was going to break my electronics.
And so I said, I'm, I'm here at your place, you know, right now I said to come outside and she said, I'm upstairs.
Well, you're on the second floor. I know that Tommy doxed her to me a long time ago.
She wasn't outside and then so that's how you got her address or apartment number.
That's how you got it from Tommy James.
What you're saying?
Plus Amber has it too. It's been around for a while.
So she admitted yes, I'm here. I'm at home.
And she said, are you going to do anything?
I said, no, I'm coming in peace.
If you want to talk, we'll talk,
but I'm not threatening you like you are.
So you were really in front of our house?
No
No, no, I wasn't there. No, right, right. Shut the fuck up. I didn't I didn't go
No, I have it in text and she said call me it's in my text
The thing is she could be cool, but I guess she was drunk because we call talk twice for hours
the first time it disconnected because I was outside and uh and and I guess it died
and then when I got home she she called me twice and we had two nice combos
and I guess she was drunk because I heard she was on good times right after that and
it was a nice combo and I I'll have a recording of one I'll send it to to uh
You'll have to play it on your end so you can hear it clearly because if I put it online here
It's it's hard to hear. It's on my phone. I have to transfer it to my computer
Okay, no laws being broken right no laws being all no not at all. She doesn't know who I know here
I mean, you know, she she doesn't know who that brother knows
We just gotta make sure with you, Iindex.
Yeah, no, no, I see Arthur and I don't wanna put it out there.
I'm just shocked that again, she was doxing my name
and doxing everybody's names again.
It's like, what's wrong with you?
We just had two good combos and I even listened to them again
and it was like, wow, she was being nice and giving advice
and stay away from Crystal and all that.
But then she gets up there and she just hate bonds with them
and kisses her ass and back and forth and I'm sick of it.
any communication with her ever again I gave her what two chances and I'm done so yeah I'm not I'm
not going to do this anymore with her or anybody that's so two-faced and it sucks I had to change
my number I trusted her with my number. You know this crazy rumor they said there was a three-way
I think let's go relationship between you Alice and then, you know, Crystal and I'm like, there's no way
They and me are not gay. I've always just been with guys
I think I was hit on in college and you know, but I'm I'm sorry, but I'm against that
You know, I was 19 and that picture you see on my profile on YouTube not the one here on the on the live
That's me in college and that's the guy that I married, Greg, that was sitting next to me.
Oh, no, Doug, come on. Okay, you still wear him? You still wear him?
That's why you got the photo as your profile picture.
And on the regular profile on YouTube, that's me and my college friends.
And Greg, that was next to me, is the guy I married. Oh, my God.
Yeah. And the t-shirt I have is from France because I went to Sorbonne University for the
My family, and I do, I made a lot of money too.
I got a great 401k plan and I'm bored because I was retiring after I got sick.
But I want to go back to work and my sister's making like $300,000.
So it's just there every two months now.
I might get into that because my brother-
Why don't you go work with Amber at the security?
They don't make much money in security.
But I've got plenty of money and plus my mom.
How much money do you want to make a month?
Right now, I'm living off my family's money and my 401k plan because my mom's dad was
a politician in Bolivia.
He was exiled twice from what my dad said.
Politician.
That's why my sister and my other siblings drive around with those, what is it, those
government plates or whatever that they say I should have?
No.
So yeah, so I'm fine. We, we all are, you know, and then my other brother owns his own business.
He makes a lot of money and he's always taking his entire family on the Norwegian cruises every summer.
And he already got him a second Corvette that his wife once gone because, you know, they have kids.
Man.
What you're saying is you're protected. Are you saying you're protected by the Bolivia government?
No, I'm not saying that.
I said, no, my sister, you know.
Yvonne Morellis?
No, no, no, no, this is from Bolivia.
The guy that she was engaged to before my dad
became president of Bolivia twice, first time was in 1993.
I was the one that was supposed to tell him
that my mom passed away.
And we had a long talk, you know?
He reached out.
He told me about my dad and how he didn't didn't understand why my my mom left him for a an American and came to the States and I want to be an American.
And then she said and Alex said I'm Canadian. I've never been to Canada. I was born here in the States.
I wish I was born in another country like my two youngest siblings. My sister. We did go back to Bolivia and my sister was born there.
And my youngest was born in another country, and me and the brother that's a year younger than me, we were born in the States.
May I say something?
Your life is very interesting.
Oh, it is. That's why people tell me I should write an autobiography. My cousin did.
And he's all over YouTube with it and I think honestly I think I think you should get the license plate
Put on just in case because you don't know what Alex capable of and with that play you can be protected. You know
under the government because I like my sister's connected with a lot of people me I just try to live
you know I became and I came into drugs and stuff so my life was different and you know
I'd like being on my own even though we had plenty of money and stuff and people know it
we got to travel around the world because of my dad's job and somebody was asking if you're
schizophrenic because a lot of the things that you say sound like they're not real
Oh, no, it's real. It's real. And people that know me know it's real, Arthur. No, I have anxiety. I had major. No, I've been diagnosed, you know, it's anxiety, major depression. Um, and that's it.
we're just doing I think that was Brandon oh hell no yeah cuz I cuz Sam
in speaks up yeah that was Brandon saying all that stuff no there's no
skit so in my family at all that's that is my life and I don't consider myself
an American and you on panel no we don't get along we just scream
And then it gets pretty big.
At least you admitted the same thing.
Goals 2026 isn't that.
Oh my god.
Dude, we're talking.
Are you fucking serious?
What once was?
Oh my goodness.
Dude, there's four people on panel.
Why would you put a video?
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, that's her video?
Oh, it's Psyche.
The volume is so loud, dude.
What the fuck?
Psyche, the volume is loud!
Oh, shit!
Adam, I used to wonder why you told them to stop the video.
Psyche!
Dude, send me one!
Welcome to the Devil's Sea.
You're telling me basically he needs a new obsession.
So you can move on from obsessing over videos.
So that fucking poor woman is gonna have to deal with the same fucking shit we know how to do it.
Why doesn't he ever go to the gay bar? That's why I'm always wondering.
Like fuck this.
Well, you were on a recap of a live two last night, so.
We didn't spare anybody what really upset me more than anything was because I, me and Tracy barely talk, you know, she's very busy, she's got a lot going on and she's been sick.
She had had the flu.
And I, you know, I today, you know.
I you know she called me and she was like be the what the fuck is going on i'm worried about christine
christine is getting back somebody alerted her and you know and she had to sit there and watch these recaps of michael
A person she actually knew way better than psyche like she was close to that guy and it's like
Seriously, you're like in you're fucking disrespecting her calling your ghetto and all this fucking kind of shit
You will have me and then you start with my fucking friends whether it's sweet pee
Tracy had a relationship with him that we didn't have and so it's a little bit
No, you know something you know the guy she did nothing but be really kind to him
You know and he came on a panel and he like totally embarrassed the fuck out of her by bringing some
And then on top of it
Thank you made a bunch of money from Michael because he was taking donations like hey, you want him clapped you can tap him for this much
So
Yeah, I just flew in yeah, he um did a his live last night. He's he's done like
You beat everybody was on
Hear it. He's a fucking loser. That's all he knows how to do
People having drama with him. It's bullshit. It's the same old bullshit all day long and it's like, yeah, like
Sweepy just coming at a sweepy machine what he knows, but
Dude, why do you keep doing that, bro?
I
Get that. This is your channel, but do those like so disrespectful
Yes, you are me we're doing we're talking and that you put a clip
That's so obnoxious. Who's that picture of it? That's supposed to be beta
What do you think?
You know, I always, I always liked you. I don't know why because a lot of people like me, baby. A lot of people like me. You know what I mean?
Because you're real. And not only that, I like that music that you put up. Remember that song that I liked and I told you I liked it and you played it.
Sing it to me. Sing it to me real quick. You remember it?
No, it was just you in the background, but it was, I'd like the theme.
I forgot I told them that I liked it.
Yeah, I played a lot of couple songs.
Yeah, they're good.
It's the kind of music I like.
It looks like she's kind of...
Are you kind of flirting with them right now?
No, really, I love that song
and I told them about it a long time ago
because I wanted it.
Can you blow on my kiss?
No, I don't know him like that. No. Come on, Arthur. Arthur, you've been weird, man.
Just because you do it. Just because you do it to Zaya and Samman don't mean. Come on, man.
Is that Crystal Marie in the back? Where's Crystal Marie? Where's Crystal Marie at? Where's she at? Where's Crystal Marie in the chat?
What's your dog, Crystal Marie?
Oh, do I miss her, bro?
That is one sexy bitch.
Oh, that is one sexy woman.
So I'll let you see a bad big bang.
What you think about crystal Karen, do you talk to crystal any which one crystal Marie Marie and I am
I don't know her but not too long ago. She kept saying on panels. Oh, I love Karen
I love Karen. I don't know why because I don't remember getting along with her, but no, I don't know her
Well, sometimes people watching you don't know they're watching your videos
You know, so maybe because I was thinking why you're even saying my name anyway, cuz I don't know you
And I'd see sometimes she goes at people.
Even Salmon asked her again,
what do you think of her?
No, I love Karen.
I don't know why.
Can you blow Aldo a kiss?
Look, she's reporting people.
She reported somebody to CPS.
Crystal, what you talk about, Crystal?
Crystal Marie, what you talk about crystal? I've never called anybody's CPS and I'm fine with the
person that thought I did it was no no she's not saying you she's not saying you she's saying
I don't know if anybody calling CPS right now on anybody I come on psyches and I'm pretty much
staying away from the other stuff and I just defend my two friends that shouldn't be mentioned by
Well, I'm just a little worried that you might you know go back to Alex, you know
No, I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm not gonna do this. That's three times that she turns on you and
And, you know, I don't even want to discuss her because I'm done and, you know, and, and
we had two nice combos the other day.
She even asked me in tags and call me and then she called me twice the first time it
disconnected because I was out and about and, you know, my phone died, but not it didn't
die.
It was the connection outside where I was.
And then she called again and we had a nice combo,
but then I realized, like somebody said,
that oh, she was only being cool because she was drunk,
that she was on good times panel.
Yeah, she's been naked, yeah, on good times.
I don't know if you knew that, yeah.
Yeah, she's on her breast, yeah, she's on her breast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, for good times, yeah.
So maybe that's why she acted like she was cool
because she was drunk.
She didn't sound drunk to me.
She was making a lot of sense.
I mean, she was on beater's drunk, you know, or she were beater wasn't alive nobody on panel and crystal got mad and did her own
Live. Yeah. Yeah, she was drunk at that moment
And I was the one that got to the talk again over a year and a half ago and she Alex even said it on the live
She said I was cool with her. She was gonna give her a chance and she did
and now that she's talking her you know crystal i mean uh beat us a lot or she's oh yeah but
she lies really be done because i've shown the proof on you i've shown your face i've shown your
text or your dm's all of that how is that fake and that was you to your friends trying to get me
And then her two ex-friends were willing to talk to her,
but she's saying one at a time, why?
She's gotta have Sam in there to be with her and one on one.
No, they wanted to go in there together, and me,
and then we'd speak, because she even invited me.
Let's all talk.
We're not gonna do a one-on-one on you,
so you can yell and lie and talk over each one of us
when your name is mentioned,
because she's involved in the bullshit.
And it's crazy because she when she was up there when when when she was up there
She said you're clean beta. You're clean beta and
She did a live she did a live and she's talking about the murder of Gigi or a legend murder of Gigi
Yeah, and and she's talking about beat a beta and Christine or something mark are clean and
You know, in reference to the murder of Gigi, I'm like, what is this bitch? It's like cottage man.
Gigi is alive. And if you mean Gia, no, everybody knows.
Gia, Gia. Yeah, Gia, Gia, Gia, my bad. Gia, man, the other thing.
I have the last text that I posted with me and her. She was going at Rick again,
and she was DMing us to call. Okay, did somebody, did somebody murder her?
No, she got back into cocaine. She got back into cocaine.
She dropped her old boyfriend and she wasn't it wasn't a mixture wasn't a mixture. You know how you do it
You know how you was doing it back in the day. She mixed it. Okay. She did a little bomb
Yeah, and she passed away and skelly talked her when she was getting high and he said be careful
And she said I am we're just partying because she got back with that x
So did anybody donate because they would be considered
Supporting, you know, support and her death, something like that.
No, because the guy, the guy she got back with was trying to use her for porn and him and his buddy were there with her.
The guy had a cam. He was there and he still was married with his wife.
So they were staying in the hotel and Gia thought, okay, I think we're going to be good again.
And then they were doing partying on Coke.
And she talked to Scali and then she went to go lay down to sleep and she never woke up because there was fentanyl in the Coke.
I'm gonna be blunt with you since you now understand it what I'm asking you
It was be the was be the one that donated the money
Perge of the bottom drugs
No, nobody donated. Nobody knew what she was doing
Okay, all I knew no as she did last live and talking about how she was done with the x and she was gonna go back with this other guy
Who she then tell the truth on because he was actually married and had kids and he was just using her because she reached out to him and he made it look like, hey, we're going to make you money. Me and my buddy and she was staying in a hotel with him because he's got a wife and kids at home.
Roy Roy Roy.
So, yeah, that's what happened. They were spent and I don't know why didn't they look in and when when did this occur?
When was when did she pass away and in in 2022 and she she was staying clean from coke
And then all of a sudden you know, so did I ever talk to her because I was around
She was doing a lot of lives and stuff and she was very
Or lives lives lives are the lines
I mean even so nobody nobody was donating to Gia ever people donated her but
if she went she was buying a lot of stuff from amazon or i mean i i said hey what's up
i'm back hey yeah because she was sick and was having pain in her back she had a lot of health
Hey, how's everybody doing good? You dropped off earlier. What happened the music? Oh
No, I just had things to do. Yeah, I'm sure more things to do go away
No, bitch. You're just not because you're bald. I
Can't stand this woman. Why?
Something about her. It's just she's just a hater like I've been nice to him and he's just been mean
This is our good girlfriend. We just don't know
Super mean to me for no fucking reason
Uh, negative.
Y'all both sound Mexican, y'all.
Hispanic, y'all.
Don't ever disrespect me ever again like that.
I don't know. He's like Italian or something.
He's fucking Mexican.
Man, I'm not Hispanic.
He's probably Mexican.
Don't leave her alone.
Exactly. Leave her alone. Leave her alone. Come on. I ain't next. Yeah, I listen to I ain't next. I think I think I this cat
There's a male cat that I feed and all and let him in and he's very vocal. Thank you
Who'd all the people backstage like me besides you one more?
I'll give him a name. I think I'll call him Arthur because I call him boy. Yeah, I
Call him boy cat
I next that's them. Yeah, because y'all are gonna be dating
Now I have a boyfriend
No, she's a boy friend. Oh my god
Come on
And it ain't me for the record. Okay. Go out in the yard. Come on. You're harassing the girl cat. Come on. Come on, Arthur, your new name is Arthur.
Hey, yo.
I've been calling him boy cat. He's a beautiful cat.
I am beautiful.
What is one of your names, Arthur?
You're right, because I'm beautiful. Thank you.
I never said that you did.
Well, she said the cat's beautiful.
Yeah, he is I put a picture
And you said yeah, so he might as well be called that
Because he doesn't have a name dumb dumb. Yeah, I just called it. I was calling your boy cat. He's a big gray cat. I
Picture of him up on my YouTube on under the community post
Now he's outside in a yard. I got a yard here. Yeah, where's old build-up?
Where did you go? Where did he go? I think he died
No, he didn't psyche. I don't know what he's doing. He went to the door to grab something and he disappeared
Maybe he got money. He would never die. He got his weakness monthly money. He got his trust on money
I went to get coffee cuz sometimes he'll do that. He'll sometimes he's still on live
He's definitely doing some oddball shit. I don't know ever since he answered that door
Man, yeah, I think he went to go get an eight ball or something
Oh, you want to go get his mess
Either calling you a method
He might have
I don't think he does math. I don't know anything. He does he gotta do something. That's something he does something
He definitely does something. I don't know what he does is weed
Yeah, yeah, me too sometimes, but I haven't smoked in a while
I need that before and after picture of him where he was the way he looked like about a year and a half ago compared to
Yeah, what do you think about those gummies? Is that knock you out? It's like I don't know if I like it though
the weed gummies
You got that beta. I think beta does done. I don't know. I don't smoke weed or consume
Man, I mean our group don't so yeah
Thanks
Yeah, they am well because I got the medical weed
Card or whatever, but that stuff is kind of weak. So I get get it from my brother who's got a hookup from
Two friends that run a dispenser in California and in Colorado Denver, Colorado too
Karen are you still connected to that hit man?
No, I'm not connected to any hit man. No, no, no. You know what happened? No, it was the dangerous brother. He was the one that threatened my other brother. He doesn't like his wife.
And he told my brother, he said,
I can get rid of that bitch
because I know this guy out of prison and he's a hit man.
So my brother and his wife stopped communicating with them
since that threat.
So that's why they haven't had anything to do with them.
He said it, but no, I don't know hit men, he does.
And I never said my brothers are hit men.
He said it and so that hurt him and then he was sending people in suits to their house
Like the FBI or something banging the gate and so they won't communicate with them at all
Where did that bald bitch Arthur though? I
Thought fucking psyche kid y'all too
No, I said I was gonna be back
So we're welcome. What wasn't you the one that used to come up here with that guy? I forget his name or a mom mistaken
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you a JT right
My boyfriend, yeah, yeah, he still comes up or
Now he doesn't come up anymore. He doesn't do panels anymore. He got bored of it. Oh
Okay, what community did you come from you don't want that came from the guy that died community, right?
Marty Marty Marty, or is it Marty?
Marty okay, then
So what community do you come from then you have you have to have come from?
We come from they call it the elder verse. I don't know
What yeah, like
What are you? Oh
Elder like old people elder. Yeah elder
also with the Shannon
Like Shannon and well not really Shannon, but you know like I don't know if you know Billy Hayden
Jarl Wigan JC
Those people
Okay, I think I do
Okay, it's like a like a chat like in Times Square Times Square chat. It used to be Vegas
Is it still going on right now? Do they still go live? What the fuck? So she's still with JT. So she
still with JT. I remember if somebody was after him and shit and then they just disappeared,
like both of them. Sorry. Somebody was after both of them. I remember somebody was at this.
So was somebody after y'all like our info because I remember y'all were here one moment and they
got disappeared and shit. Well, it's not like we come like it's we don't make it our full lives,
We don't come on panels often
Okay
No, but nobody's after us. I mean like people try but you know, they don't have nothing on this. So
Yeah, they'll try whatever real real relationships, too. So that's good that you know, y'all don't come on
Yeah, because like we try not to put stuff out there publicly, you know, yeah
Because that's what you wouldn't have met on internet. I remember y'all saying I believe right y'all met like on and chat and shit
We didn't meet on a chat. I mean we chatted, but you know, we met each other in real life and then we dated
So that's how it happened
Good otherwise people would be coming at you like salmon or
Well, people have tried it salmon tried, but you know, he's
He's so fucking dumb
Yeah, well, that's why people are entertained by him because he's dumb. You know I'm saying like he's slow, you know
Like you gotta have low and he's like a guy that's fun visited in drama like he's he acts like a woman like
Like a mean girl
and you know what?
Yeah, he is slow and I don't know
Somebody said that beta made that community post for him because no way can he ride or talk like that?
What community post something he posted on his new channel community post and it was obviously written by
Beta because there's no way he can or chat GPT or chat GPT, maybe I don't think I mean or
Or his brother or his brother
You know brother's broom game. So I know you knew that right Karen
Yeah, I knew that is he intelligent or is he slow like Sam and nice a little smarter a little smarter
But you know like nobody has our location. We moved down to Mexico anyway, so nothing matters
Oh
Y'all got fucking the porter girl
No, we voluntarily left the country
No, so she got she did it voluntarily, but one of them
Don't have their stuff that I'm come on my dumb brother. I know what's going on right now Trump going crazy right now
I mean, we're American, but we went down there voluntarily because that country's thoughts.
You know what?
And most people that are born in another country, like my sister and my younger brother, they
were born in other countries, and they're able to have dual citizenship.
Yeah, that's what we did
But see I was born here in the States and so was my other brother the one year younger than me and all we can have is
American Citizenships, it's like shit. I well as long as you have one parent. That's like Mexican like you can inherit, you know
Well, my mom was actually born in Bolivia and my dad American, but I was born in the state
So I can do that somehow get a dual citizenship if I decide to get out of this country because I don't like the state
Oh, I'm going to look into it because I read that Jolie, what's her, um, Brad Pitt's ex-wife, Jolie, whatever her name is, her, Jolina Jolie, Jolina, yeah, her, she got their, uh, young, their daughter that looks like Brad to get a dual citizenship in Canada because one of the parents was born there.
That's what they said. So I can do that. Yeah. Yeah, you can't. Yeah.
You know, I mean, my parents are both gone now. I wish I would have
To do that you gotta go to the consulate. That's like in your area or you have to go to Bolivia to do it
Yeah, and my my sister was born in Bolivia. So she has a dual citizenship
Your green card still good Karen my what your green card
No, I don't have a green card. I was born here. Oh, you're born here
Well, you you said I know but you was talking about how your sister has something like the license plate thing
I forget what that shit's called
Because of my mom's family, you know, I guess if they are somebody important in another country
They can get it here because she always has to have it me. I just use regular license plates. I'm I don't care
About that shit and she goes to South America a lot and she her Spanish is bad me
I'm the only one that remembered all
Right chat, what is that called when you're protected?
Well, you're from another country or whatever. What is that shit called?
Like you got certain plates and shit like that. That's what I'm trying to get. I know one of y'all
Protects them. I just thought she was using that to show off. I don't know why she gets it. She gets it
I guess I could get it. I don't care for that
You know plus this is Texas. There's crazy people
Why would I want to use the consulate plate or whatever that she uses her and my younger brother?
You know me and the brother that's a year younger than me. We don't bother with that shit
You know, we were both born in the States and she barely speaks Spanish. I'm the one that remembered three languages fluently
You know, I'm the oldest
And, you know, I wish I could have a there go there go diplomats their diplomats is your sister diplomat her husband or whatever you know
diplomatic immunity like father was he was a diplomat and and a lot of the my mom's family besides her dad and then her ex was president of Bolivia twice.
And she left him for an American and the guy tried to get her back when she was pregnant
with me and he said, just leave him now and I'll raise your baby when the baby's born
as my daughter.
So that's why I was the one that had a telling that she passed away and my dad told me to
contact him because his name was never supposed to be mentioned in our home until after my
mom died.
And, you know, JT and I have haters and they, they're jealous that we have a relationship
outside of YouTube.
So they say like, oh, Rain and JT are brother and sister, is that brother, some shit like
that.
Yeah, I remember that.
Yeah.
But the thing is, y'all go wild.
Y'all been, y'all, y'all known for saying the craziest shit too, y'all like a pirate
couple of fucking evilness.
Yeah, but like make it make
Yeah, but like make it make sense like how could we be brother and sister we met like on YouTube it doesn't make sense
Different right and shit
So who started that rumor?
It was Jarl Wigan, but you know, it's whatever
That's very good. Yeah, we know we don't we don't take shit personally
Now what is it man?
That is a weird rumor to start though. Oh my god. I got to be in YouTube and then fucking saying I'm you know
I haven't started with it, of course, so whatever
Doesn't affect us
In our relationship. Yeah, that's good. You guys are stronger than most people
Yeah, so what's up with y'all?
Not a damn thing. Just on panel psyche fucking. I don't know what's up. It's like I know where it's like you go
He left me on with that Joe Shipley one night, and I don't like Joe shit. I don't know. He's not a talkative guy
Yeah, I think I like that either
When he's off that liquor who Joe oh Joe. Yeah, Joe's where Joe be on that he only cuz Joe really only Joe only
Really comes up when he's tipsy, you know, I'm saying well most
Of the IP2 community, that's what they do, you know, saying they they typically are on panel when they're tipsy
It's like they can't be on panel and they're not tipsy. It's crazy. And then he must be tipsy or drunk all the time because he's always drunk
Yeah, Joe, Joe's creepy like you try hitting on me. I'm like, what are you doing?
You have a beautiful voice. I just I was wondering we're psyche because I was ready to jump off of there. The guy was drunk
And, well, yeah, we just, you and me, and it's like, damn, you know, I think I did drop off and so, you know, it was a horrible experience.
Let's go story to you.
Oh, he goes talk. Yeah. He was adding me to Crystal's panel and so I, so I'm sorry, but that pissed me off. So I've been talked to him. And then Psyche gets on and says, well, he says he's your woman. Yeah. He was getting a little too deep because I've never, I don't know him. He sounded cool, but he's too much into these trolling on panels.
He likes his voice. His voice is like nails on a chalkboard.
Oh, I didn't say anything about his voice.
I mean, he sounded cool and stuff.
And then until he got me in the panel,
it's like, damn, you know, and so I ended up blocking him.
I'm not going to play this game.
And I don't have time to be on all these panels, you know,
all night long like he does.
And then he texts me or call me all night long
when I'm asleep.
Oh, is that a new vape cycle?
Yeah, yeah, there's three times.
You guys send me a screenshot of that.
I'll probably get that vape.
See it's three kinds sells how many blinkers you've had through it. That is awesome. Yeah, send me that cuz I guess
That my younger brother can get it for me. Is it is it weed?
Yes, I'm talking shit about my blankers, huh? It's called boutique cells boutique
But is it we either was three kinds of weed strawberry
Hold it up again. What's that?
What's he without the e at the end like bo uti q okay there? I could that took a picture of it
Yeah, I'll see your resume. It's a resume. I think I think you're a diplomat
I'm having this episode transcribed with a spider ritual
Spider ritual, but if you want to hear yo, that really stuck. That's kind of how that stuck that really bobbed you the spider shit
Like that was only a joke man
It wasn't I started that like that. It was just a joke brother. Like you gotta let it go man
The spider thing just blew up man, it's all the joke
Although you asked the question my mom's um her uncle was in uh, bolivian the ambassador of bolivia in england in london
Yeah, that was a few years ago. You got to use that power you got to use that power
No, she knows I don't care about that. I mean they're gone, you know, it's like
Basically they could get away with murder. I think my grandmother did
your grandmother. I knew, I knew y'all. Come on, man. Her husband, my, your grandmother had to be. Oh,
and she got away with it. They may disappeared because, um, or somebody disappeared because my
grandfather had an affair with them. And so people have been, my dad was scared of my grandmother.
She passed on. She could be a dangerous person and powerful too, but she was dangerous.
Hey, I'll be right back mafia type right mafia. Yeah, I'll be right back. I was scared of her
Combo's man. Good combo. I
Like the fact that rain don't like salmon, you know and JT, you know, and I like that. Yeah, they don't don't like them, you know
I like that. Yeah, I don't like him because he believes everything Bita says and it's a lot a lot of lies and maybe that's why she doesn't want to panel up with the two ex friends together, one on one because she wants to take control, I guess.
Because they'll speak the truth.
And she wouldn't share that with Barb because they weren't that close with Barb because she'd always try to be messy with them and all.
All right, so it's Barbara big liar. Like does she lie a lot a lot, you know, yes
She's aggressive. She's a very assertive. So she is dangerous. So, you know, Christine, right?
She's like the better version of Christine because Christine is fucking annoying, you know, she thinks you know it all
Oh my god, when I was on a discord with her, she was scared. So yeah, but but it upsets me that you're
Yeah, it upsets me that you're telling me that she's, you know, lies a lot, you know,
because that, you know, that's no good, you know, she knows to be.
I thought she was telling me the truth about the 5150.
Did I even share that?
And look at what happened.
And then Crystal's such a liar.
She was on somebody's panel saying, what was it?
Janie made that up about the 5150.
No, it was Barb.
And I did a recording with her permission.
We had an interview that she wanted me to post.
And I did.
It came from Barb.
But Barb even admitted it finally on Crystal's panel, and she said that she had a 5150 once.
She said, I didn't say it happened twice. But her friend,
Bita's ex-friend said that's bullshit because they were closer to Bita, and none of that was said.
And why would she tell Barb that? So that's one thing they defend about Bita, that there is no
5150 done, and the truth about Barb taking money from all of them.
You know, she was staying on her sister's couch, her husband had left her, it was during COVID and she didn't even have a car and she'd walk to Ben and Jerry's after they'd cash up her money because she was getting ice cream every day for herself and she was sleeping on her sister's couch.
I think she's doing better now, I don't know, but this was during COVID because her husband had just left her.
You know, and that's the truth I can show that to but you know
They just need to shut up and stop bringing me and my friends names up and that's crystal and see I even have a text
She didn't show her whole text
Because she said I want to talk to Nancy and Jamie and she goes I won't mention you guys a name again
But there she is yelling our names because we we've blocked her for good. We don't want shit to do with her
And she thinks that's gonna bring people back. No, we're done
And it took me a while to open my eyes to that.
I was talking to this bitch for 10 months.
She was blowing me up when I was at the ICU
and they'd bring me the phone in the mornings
and there's all these missed calls
and then I'd hear the messages, I need you coming back.
It's like, bitch, I mean ICU and you know it.
I mean, why are you bothering me?
You know, she didn't respect that.
Then I got into the physical rehab a lot of work
You know, I didn't know what was happening to me, you know, and so I worked out every
day because I needed to be back on my feet.
I wasn't, I needed to be gone from there.
They said if I didn't recover, I'd be stuck there.
and I made it and two months later, I was discharged.
So, but she'd be bothering me then
during the physical workout and the therapist,
he'd say, who's that?
Why is your phone ringing?
And it was Crystal.
I answered, Crystal, you know,
physical therapy till two o'clock, stop calling.
Oh, it's an emergency, this and that.
You know, always the bullshit with internet.
And she's always lying and she'll make up stories like,
my mom, her mom was dying last week, she said.
Her mom was not dying.
her mom had, I think she almost had COVID and she was fine. And like her grandmother, oh,
she's dying. But then when they had the funeral, she's over there in her car on IG Live, dancing
the Britney Spears. And I called her, I said, what are you doing, Crystal? You were crying about
your grandmother. And now you're celebrating. Aren't you supposed to be at the funeral? Oh,
You know for attention when she's desperate for attention just because
What's his name the Q 45?
He didn't want to talk to her and she was telling him on panel
I need you to call me and he said I'm not gonna call you. He said I'm like I don't talk to you outside
It's an emergency see did she does this for attention when she's being called out and there's nothing going on
Oh, that whole situation was because she had a passing in her family the whole situation where she ended up going back to be the same man
always and then she's doing that again recently. So which family member is dying now? Now she's
saying her mom. Her mom is fine. Her mom almost had like COVID and she wasn't even there for her mom.
You know, and and Brendan Q talked to her dad and the dad told them the truth like he told everybody else before that crystal
Comes over to their house banging on the door yelling at them
And when he lets her in and they get into an altercation
So he calls he said I'm calling the police on you because she goes nuts
and she'll start hitting herself in her face loudly
for when he's on the phone with the police
and said, he's hitting me, he's hitting me, he's hitting me.
That's how crazy she is.
And she does this shit for attention.
She doesn't do real life, Eldo.
She doesn't even know her neighbors.
You know, she complained about a dog being loosed outside.
And I said, well, Crystal, go to your neighbor
and see if he belongs to that.
Oh, I don't know them.
I said, you don't even know your own neighbors?
You know her whole life. I've even seen videos of her falling asleep
Of her on the phone with discord on and she'll be sleeping and one guy that she
Hooked up with was filming her and then you could hear her like dreaming discord
Like and he said he's even said it's wack and you know what those videos are up on YouTube. I'm gonna go ahead and share them
She's obsessed with the internet and and she doesn't do real life
Yeah
And she just yells her names like she thinks we're gonna just forgive her and go back to her because she does this over and over again
She's a sick sick person. Yes, I did sense that some of her lives to her sister who she had as
Contact on FB because she didn't want shit to do with her
And she got mad. Oh, she's harassing my family. No, your siblings don't talk to you, Crystal. And you even said it all over texts and DMs that you just found out that the reason her parents won't have her over for Christmas is because that's when her siblings are there, and they don't want anything to do with her since COVID.
And that's why Crystal only sees them after Christmas
and Crystal just found out
that that was the reason why her siblings.
I have that in text where she's bitch.
I even posted it and she acts like nobody sees it.
Maybe they don't, even her aunt.
She said, my aunt hates my dad.
He's a bad person and here's proof.
And the proof she showed me that it's a DM with her aunt.
Why aren't they texting?
And on the DM, she's bashing her dad to the aunt.
And the only thing the aunt said was,
Crystal, your family said your name
is never supposed to be mentioned in their home.
That was all she said.
Where was she bashing her dad?
And I have that, I even posted that.
I posted that, Eldo.
Yeah, that's crazy.
You know, and salmon and then they'll look.
It's like, shit, I show proof.
And she gets away with it. Oh, she's harassing me bitch. I have all all these texts and you calling me
I mean, I I have that on if you pick up my videos, you'll see all that there
I've even put it in my community posts and videos and
She's still running with her. She's harassing me bitch. You were blowing me up. I blocked you everywhere
And let me ask you this
Look, let me ask you to be honest Karen. This is an open time
So so why do you call be the randomly here and there just be honest like
Her two friends wanted we're ready to go on panel about it and then she was she went nuts Jamie and bar Jamie and Nancy. Yes. Yes
But, but if she told you like, I don't want nothing to do with them, you just said, fuck
what you think and say it.
I just want to call you.
That's why I don't talk to her anymore.
And now she says that she's wanting them to take a link.
Well, they're not anymore because she's too messy.
You know, and I told them just don't even bother defending her because, and they said,
you know, she is a whack job because she, I mean, she was trying, she, she wanted a
community to help, you know, because she grew up being bullied.
That time when Oceans did a live on her,
she had Nancy up and Ashley Ray,
all her ex-friends were up and so were Barb,
and it was about Bita,
and her and I were on the phone and on text,
and she just got silent.
She was hurt and upset and I said,
well, they're asking you to join.
Are you going to join?
She was upset and she didn't want to join,
and it hurt her when she saw Jamie joined.
It was about her and ever since then she decided to do her channel and she was
Fucked with on on Skelly's cuz she she'd use him as a her muscles. She threatened people say well
I'm gonna go on Skelly's why don't you come up with scale? Oh, well beta beta you see Skelly as her muscle
Yeah, and oh my god
He was sick of her shit and then one time
she was trying to use his channel and act all bullies and
Q45 joined with her real picture
and he fucked with her and she was practically crying and then Trisha Licious joined and attacked her then
and then after that he made a youtube account and then she got with saman and uses him to be her
simp or whatever because everybody knows the truth about her you know she's now now be honest with me
the number be the number was that given to you by her or did you just find it
We used to talk a year ago before I got sick because I remember one time she called me and we talked about our cats and she called me and I said, guess what, I said, I'm right in front of this restaurant, it's a Persian restaurant and I read her the name and she goes, are you going to go there?
And I said, no, I'm just passing it up. And she was telling me about the foods that they have and I said, I'll check it out sometime, but you know, I said it was weird because she called me and there I was right in front of that restaurant.
And we were fine then, but it was lately,
because she got caught being shady with Sherry too.
She's very controlling.
She did block Sherry because Sherry was talking
to somebody else that Bita doesn't like.
And she blocked her.
And she would yell at her on the phone on three-way call,
are you talking to someone selling, yeah, no, no, no.
She's very manipulative.
And controlling and then she lies and says, oh, I don't have a problem who sherry talks to yes, you did and crystal was on that call to when she was yelling at sherry.
For being in communication with somebody and blame me for me putting them together because they were friends before you know all I said well if you missed her and your friends reach out to her apparently she did and then all of a sudden crystal calls beta and has it all on there for beta to yell at her at sherry.
All right, so who's manipulative?
Bita, very manipulative.
Very controlling.
When you say she's manipulative,
do you mean like when she starts to cry,
when she's talking to people to make them feel
sad and care about her?
Yeah, exactly, just like that.
Because she did that with us.
She had me petting her ex-friends one time, crying.
And so I did and she was this fake crying and made it all about herself and she wouldn't let them talk.
She screamed over them and then she hung up. She doesn't let people talk.
So yeah, but lately ever since the Sherry thing, no, we haven't been good. And yes, I did reach out to her.
And they were ready to go panel up until she, they said she announces you'll do it one on one. Why? What does she have to hide? You know, she doesn't want the truth to come out about other things that they may mention.
So they don't care for her anymore. And, you know, they're letting it go. Who cares what Barb says they don't care for Barbie there.
You know yesterday because even Nancy said it she said I'm ready to join now and I'll say you are so I even posted
You know, we're ready to join
Until be done made that statement it went on one. So no
And she had me fight with one of them I mean for a long time, but we're good finally I just didn't trust
that one person
that Crystal try to break up a friendship between me and Nancy, who've been friends for a long time and there's never been drama.
Because, although she does real life, she was out showing me her e-bike and she was charging at her and her husband got new e-bikes.
And there, Crystal was blowing me up about drama and trying to involve her.
Well, Nancy, I said, Nancy's on the phone with me. She's out with her family and they're charging their e-bikes.
Yeah, they stopped mentioning Nancy Nancy's happily married and her kid graduated with top honors, you know from university and she posted a video about that.
She's out of the loop with the stuff going on but she notices that crystal saying her name to
Regrets that she ever gave crystal a chance because she said crystal was always batshit crazy and and then she tried to break up our friendship by having Nancy patch her in when I was in ICU.
And then I found out that you know why she wanted me to patch into me.
Because she was, she was trying to use me to go against somebody named brighter Chucky who now she unlocked.
Crystal is sick. She doesn't do real life and it's all about hate bonding. She doesn't have any real life friends. She doesn't even have her siblings. She hasn't seen her nephews since COVID.
That's crazy, but that was real. That was beta. That's what you're saying. That was beta. That was real. That's what you're saying. That was real.
Yeah.
you went a lot of me, would you?
No, I'm not.
And the thing is, she's the one that put out,
Abba was done with her.
I had a video of Abba going off at her,
calling her crazy and she trusted her.
And she was the one that put out the information
of that Abba was had an escort, she was an escort
and she put it out and told Gamble that.
So Abba left YouTube.
went away because she was embarrassed and it was all because of Vita being evil and having people
share that. I think she, somebody you know is the one that shared it for her and gave it to
DX and so they were posting all that site and everything and Abba was embarrassed though you
So, yeah, there's a lot of that shit Bita did, you know, she is controlling manipulative and if I have to show the rest on her, I will, you know, because she just lies too much.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
Oh shit, I'm getting a call Terry. I gotta answer this call. I gotta answer this call.
Yeah, no, sure. Okay.
Hey you. Hey bully cat.
Boy cat is outside.
You wanna go to the yard? Huh?
You're just gonna lick yourself.
So cute.
I'm gonna leave in an hour and a half, baby.
I love you.
Uh huh. I love you. Love you too. Oh. This is a bully cat right here with me. I love it. So cute. She's kissing her so she's been good with the other cats. I mean she was terrorizing the new baby and and the boy cat but she's calm now but she did his at him a little while ago so he's in the yard.
Yeah, I need transcribe this episode, but this was a great episode
This was when uh, this is when they did a spider bitch you along me and you can see they all start doing it
Almost a whole lot was about me, but you can hear
That guy in the picture with no teeth. What's what is that? It's Casey. That's a guy that you're the guy that dates his own death
That's him
Yeah, oh he picked the death. Yeah, but then he came back from the dead and like, you know
Here we go here here they say about me when I'm like Christine's dog. That's cute
It's fuzzy bear. Yeah, the sweepies is doing parodies and is a form of comedy and then beta
being like telling him like all the time, leave me alone.
And he still continuously wants to make clips on her.
And then Alexandra, the whole thing.
And I was like, yo, he went over to money for 20s yesterday
and he sat there and was, he was sitting up there
trying to play a cool and all this other stuff.
Somebody aired his dumb ass out.
They was like, yo, bro, you don't sensationalize,
you know, unalloying yourself.
Oh, well, you know, everybody in me and, you know,
y'all don't see anything to beat up.
they shut the fuck up dude you in your mid 40s and the same bullshit. I've never told him anything
like that he makes up stories nobody just because his feelings are hurt on the internet doesn't mean
he needs to make a post that he's gonna not want to be here because of whatever you know I've never
I understand that I don't like him.
He brings attention to his channel.
Look, listen, I understand I don't like him,
but that shit right there had maybe
lose a lot more respect for him
because you just don't do shit like that, yo.
If he was to unalive himself,
he wants people to have a guilt trip
on you and Alexandra
all because of a strike on his channel.
Like, you understand how insane this insane this shit is?
You were like you're threatening to unalive yourself because of a fucking channel, bro.
You such grass. Somebody told me today, he was telling Christine that Christine.
on all the lives of people.
Like some wild shit, am I mistaking?
I don't know.
This is what I don't know if-
No, you're right.
No, you and I do rituals.
He's-
I made it short of it.
I just made it short.
Thank you.
If you could spare with your traffickers?
Yeah.
Yeah, spare with your traffickers.
If you could spare with your witches.
Yeah.
Hospital, you killed many people.
That's what I don't understand.
He says his name is Cult of Psyche.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
It's like shit like and talks about the fucking um, I don't know what they call it. You can't call it illuminati
But then like you have a question up. Hey, you have you have fucking Krishna on your fucking background
Gee, what the fuck are you talking about? Yeah, you have the Kali Ma in the back is your background picture, dude
What is fucking talking about bro? You'd love demonic shit
Talking about oh, uh, I'm like Jesus get the fuck out of here, dude. Oh
Yeah, you're making a blast me towards Jesus, that's not cool G
Yeah. He referenced himself to that. Again, nowhere near Jesus. I don't I see. I that's a crazy thing. I was so sweet. I I missed most of everything that happens overnight. I know he does his lives like I don't know from 12 to I don't know whatever.
I thought that it was what was it?
Psyche Awakens, where he did terror cards.
Now it's just like a drama panel where I'm going to just keep poking at people.
That one, nothing to do with me.
has zero self-awareness, no boundaries, and anybody that goes up there and tries to like
camp for him and give him his McDonald's and tell him, oh, oh, you're being bullied. Oh,
you're whatever this and that. You guys are either buddy-chilling him or you're fucking some
dumb weekend motherfucking people. Yo, you ever hear of smack when he eats his food? I just think
You know what I mean?
I'm like, yo, that's the shit I enjoy.
I can't lie.
Lord, you chew your food with your mouth shut.
I used to be put there.
Just don't chew your food on the wall for that shit.
That's a developmental milestone and some lip smacking is in.
It's goodness.
It's not just goodness.
Hey, it's Tracy.
Hello, Tracy.
Hi, Tracy.
I'm so Tracy.
Tracy.
I'm so glad you're here.
I'm just, I, I'm really, really upset. And those pictures of crystal.
Karen.
why did you call me yesterday again because they were ready to take your
panel who are they who are they Jamie and Nancy why do you call what do you call
my number I'm gonna play your audio right now yeah go ahead and you alright so
you can't be on panels lying to people when you're off my ass you've been
kissing my ass trying to talk to me and I don't want to talk to you
to talk to you. They wanted to join your panel. That's not what the voicemail says. Yes, I did. I
say that. All right, Karen, since you're so good with my pictures being used, I'll use yours as a
thumbnail today too. So tell your fuckface. You're going to use an old picture? I'll show your real
picture that everybody said. You knew that.
Do you want to take the rest back up go ahead and take it drop her man
I'll use that token because remember I had ten. I thought you said last time
Yeah, yeah, just leave her off of there. She's drama. So they're not gonna join anymore. They're gonna defend her against Barb
Yeah
Barber is still talking about her getting 51 50
They were pissed off and they were gonna defend her and yes, I called her because they wanted to take her panel
They wanted her to know
going to give her a call
you know, I guess not. I
her directly. So I did ca
And I told her that they're going to take the panel and, you know, to talk to her.
There are many things you called her. She's like, she's going to be exposing what you left for her yesterday.
Well, what did I say? All I said was that, you know, because it's wrong, you know, I felt bad because I put it out there with Barb saying that she had a 5150 done.
And those two are pissed off and they hate Barb and they said she's a liar and they were ready because even Nancy said, I'm ready to take panel right now.
And I said, well, then call Vita.
She was scared, and I made the mistake of calling.
That's it.
And she was talking about pictures.
I didn't say anything about her picture recently.
My calls are, you know, I'll go ahead and play what I said,
because that's on there, you know?
So I don't know why she's, you know,
they were going to help her out, because they're sick of it.
They're sick of Barb.
And that's why they were going to join her panel,
and Nancy was scared to call her.
You know, she's gonna flip out like that and just be messy. I mean shit
Does she want me to play the recordings I have on her and especially when she was on panels shouting that
Jamie and Ashley Ray and then goes back and forth with Astro who sent me the recordings of her threats to her
You know, but I don't like this back and forth, but yeah, I was all for it. I was gonna go ahead and say look
I'm sorry that I did the interview with Barb and these two know the truth
And they were gonna tell the truth that she was never 51 50 because they were closer to her than Barb was and
Barb is over there hurrying crystal or saying their names over and over again because they don't want shit to do with her and
Crystal only posted Nancy's part of a conversation
And they showed me the real conversation, and I posted it.
So Crystal is bad shit crazy, there's nothing going on.
She plays this game like, oh, there's something going on with my family when she wants attention, because she makes it all about herself.
Well, but I also have a communication from a long time ago Vita wanting me to send it to gamble and said
Don't tell him where it came from or whatever, but send it as it is
So I sent it to him exactly how it was and she was real upset with me. I have all that saved
So she wants to go there and we'll go there
But last year we were cool because, like I said, I stopped by, I was right by that
Persian restaurant.
That was before I got sick and we even had a nice convo and she was telling me about
different kind of Persian foods if I ever decided to stop there to eat.
She's helpful one day and then turns against you the next person.
Yeah, and then she just turns against people and it's like, you know, and what I have in
You know, she's from Iran or whatever and grew up in the States and, you know, and also we have a lot of similarities and that's what I liked about her but yeah, she wants to go there and she hasn't seen me I'll come up because you see me on cam.
Yeah
I mean they say they've been this the spider ritual continues here like check it this out real quick
Why would you even feel that white beat it
Anybody that
I'll join her about beta
Yeah, summer, she's a good person, you know, she does a lot of work for the homeless people and everything. So we're good.
And so I shared her channel and she had an issue with beta. So maybe she wants to go there and then, you know, then I'll be out on her. So.
I don't know what her issue is her whole life is the internet and lives. It's like beta do real life. You need to step out and talk to real people touch grass.
Firework show on 4th of July. She didn't even go celebrate. She's she was on live showing lights out in the sky or whatever
You know, what kind of life is that?
Yeah, and it's triggering so I'm not on 24 seven like she is you know, we do real life
I come on your panels. I'm pretty much don't join other panels
There's a bunch except for summer and I already know what she you know luck what she had to say about beta
And I didn't say anything about beta
So but summer is a good person
Yeah, I don't know beta just wants to fight and she needs to get off the internet for a few minutes at least
You know, she's all over the place
But I can show everything on her and she out what's she gonna do just crying a Kia all of that his Facebook
What he said about her he left her because she wouldn't like leave the internet and he'd be yelling at her in the background
And she wouldn't get off. She was still on on the either on calls with the people on the internet
And then her dad even fired her because she wasn't showing up to her job.
And all her friends who can attest to that, so she wants to go there, I will show everything.
And I'm not afraid to come up, I do it on private, on phone with people, and everybody
knows I've changed, you know, I look great compared to her.
I don't have skin tags all over my eyes.
I have a clear picture of the skin tags too, should I post that?
And then when she puts makeup on,
you can still see the crater face.
And she did get with captain content.
He said that she offered him $25 if he keeps quiet about it.
Oh my God.
So yeah.
I mean, it's like, you know,
someone's asking about like, oh, oh, like,
one thing, you know, guys, you can buy clap tokens,
but my clap tokens, when you buy them,
you have immunity with them too.
And so, you know,
For like for like and so remember you said that had the 10 last time on yours too. Yeah, you have you know if you left and so
Yeah, so yeah
Facts about that, you know doing that any way to people though, you know, I mean if you're gonna be an asshole
I I would kick him, but you know, just
Monetize the the hate a little bit because it's like it is like, you know, I'm demonetized right now. There's not people really don't
Why did she stalk you so much though? She's in she's obsessed with you
Why is she always in your chat when you go live and everything? She's obsessed with you. No, I know
Yeah, I mean it's a good turn around where I'm talking her and that kind of thing where everybody sees it. It's her
Yeah
Yeah, you know and and and I was the reason that that Alex was cool with her the last time and yes
I have the proof of her sending all this information on and well
It wasn't she wasn't doxing Alex. She was telling me the court to go to this court or whatever here where I'm at
You know, she's shady as fuck and I gave her chance and yes, I called her twice because of the two friends
They were ready to, even Nancy, she told me,
I'm ready to, you know, can you let Bita know?
And she was afraid to call Bita,
and I made the mistake of contacting Bita twice.
Yeah, well, we all make mistakes, I guess.
Yeah, you know, so I'll let him know.
I'm sure they're gonna be watching this
and say, you know what, you're right.
No, it was a bad idea.
They were just wanting to defend her, especially to Crystal,
who keeps saying her names and told me in the text that I did have a screenshot of.
Yeah, I want to talk to Nancy and Jamie.
Then she said, what was it?
God, it was something I posted it and she pretty much had a lot to say.
Yeah.
She went to use Sam and to take him away from Bita to be her simp.
Those were her words
Yeah, oh, and she said oh and I won't mention you all again and then there she is mentioning everybody again
So I posted that that text were showing that because she wasn't gonna show that
Yeah, no, and she was in that chat. She thought it was just a group chat and she was in that chat with the
Ashley Ray, where they were getting graphic.
Everybody was there.
Nancy wasn't there.
It was Jamie, Tricia Lictus, Barb, you know,
because yeah.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for the cash app.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that so much.
I had somebody's birthday cake, perfect.
I had somebody that I clapped to.
Okay, gotcha.
Thank you so much. You're known. I'm doing prepaid tokens. So don't worry. No, and you're safe. Yeah. No, no, yeah
No, I'm just yeah
I'm gonna hop off in a little bit anyway cuz we're gonna go get some margaritas at a Mexican restaurant
Okay, we have happy hour. It's four o'clock. So yeah, so I'm gonna jump off. She just needs to do real life
You know, she lost Kia who was messing around with with some massage parlor women or whatever, you know
Well, she'd be online. I'll have all of that everything. So she wants to go there. I'll be more than happy to share everything
I was no docks and mamas. I don't docks mamas. I don't docks my donors mamas, but they have a cap token and they know
So thank you so much
Um, yeah, and um big you're in big I'm gonna take big clips out of the chat for the day. He's
now he's on time now. Yeah, okay. Yeah, okay. Thank you for being a friend Amanda and Christine
and Alex holding hands and salmon comes in
And shows them all his hook
And Dippy sounds retarded
It's probably because he is
I'm so sorry, my computer's being taken control by AI, I'm so sorry
It's our favorite thing we laugh like saints with eyeliner and a phone that never rings.
Breakfast like this in casual wealth.
We all sweat the shit like the sweet fours like the dreams.
Hey guys, should we do another?
Should I get a big coffee today?
It's like been drinking coffee since eight in the morning,
and I can get as many refills as I want.
Bita, can I have 10 streamers?
I can get another piece of coffee.
A refill run?
Yeah, we're gonna go on a refill run.
Should I go?
Actually, I can go to...
Oh, I do.
Okay, maybe I can go...
I'll transfer this one second, which I did the cash out by the way. Thank you so much
Appreciate it right now. Okay
Kerr occur
Okay
Yeah, now I have a few buckaroos. Okay, so transfer
You grab my wallet and we can go to mcdonald's, baby
withdraw
Virginia
Incent up
Kind of expensive, but okay
Done
Got money
Hold on, what did I get?
12, three coffee.
Okay, I can get a cigarette, a cigar,
and alcohol for the day.
Hey, let me throw my wallet.
We'll go.
See me?
Oh, here I am.
Okay.
I forgot the dollar bills.
Okay, bullshit.
You can still get off the get.
I know what I'll do.
Bye.
Oh, I need matches.
Stupid lighters out.
Okay, Victoria wants me to join her stream.
Well, I'm like, I walk here right now.
So it'll be like a few minutes and I'll go to the big Bethany.
We're doing a little run.
Oh my God, my hair long.
I mean, is anybody with this bunch of hair
being called so bald?
Like, look how my hair runs, we're seeing.
Like, that's the best little bird deal.
My hairline, we're seeing that bad.
I mean, geez.
You think I was like fucking, you know,
George from Seinfeld.
Okay, okay, it's a beautiful day.
Um, I should have probably gone pee before I went to this walk, but they have a bathroom in there
And they have one at McDonald's. Did you see me? Okay, here we go. Hey, here we are
My secret coffee location. Watch me steal a coffee. No, actually don't steal coffee
I actually bought this this morning. They said free repos all day
They're closed
Okay
I'm Victoria's live
Well, let's go over there. Hold on
Yeah, I need to use the bathroom in McDonald's, anyway.
Okay, I'll see you guys.
I'll get back.
Draw my everywhere, yeah.
You can go ahead and link that Nancy in my chat.
And everyone, go over there.
Stay psych.
He sent two L-Dos from his live, if you don't mind.
All right, is someone backstage?
Okay.
Catch up with me soon.